-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊字幕组==-
翻译：晓  贝殿下
校对：猫 猫
-==破烂熊字幕组==-
时间轴：卢 斌
~ 我看见树木青绿 ~
~ I see trees of green ~
~ 还有玫瑰红艳 ~
~ Red roses too ~
~ 我看见他们 ~
~ I see them bIoom ~
~ 因你我而繁盛光鲜 ~
~ For me and you ~
~ 我在心中默想 ~
~ And I think to myseIf ~
~ 多美妙的世界 ~
~ What a wonderfuI worId ~
破烂熊字幕组作品
-==http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
寻堡奇遇2:逃离关塔那摩
~ 我看见天空蔚蓝 ~
~ I see skies of bIue ~
~ 还有白云片片 ~
~ And cIouds of white ~
~ 明媚的白天 ~
~ The bright bIessed day ~
~ 漆黑的夜晚 ~
~ The dark sacred night ~
~ 我在心中默想 ~
~ And I think to myseIf ~
~ 多美妙的世界 ~
~ What a wonderfuI worId ~
~ 是啊 ~
~ Yes ~
~ 我在心中默想 ~
~ I think to myseIf ~
~ 多美妙的 ~
~ What a wonderfuI ~
爽啊 伙计!
Yes, dude!
你他妈的 你妈的 搞什么鬼啊?
What the fuck? What the fuck? What are you doing?
我只是在排泄每天的废物罢了
I'm taking the most incredibIe dump of aII time, man.
难道就不能等我洗完澡吗?
You couIdn't wait tiII I got out of the shower?
你不记得了么? 我们刚吃了三十个汉堡
May I remind you that we both just ate 30 burgers...
还有四大份炸薯条
and four Iarge orders of fries?
别担心 你也快轮上了
Don't worry, in a IittIe bit, I'm sure it'II hit you too.
也许吧 但我会等你先滚出去再说
It may be. But I'm gonna wait tiII you get out of the shower.
那别等太久了 我们一小时内得去机场的
WeII, don't wait too Iong. We've got to Ieave for the airport in an hour.
噢 好热啊
Ooh, that burns.
一小时?      对 还有 罗迪
An hour?         Hey, and, RoIdy?
怎么了?
Yeah?
琶真漂亮
Nice pubes.
混蛋 赶快给我滚出去
AsshoIe, get out of here right now.
伙计 这玩意儿可真大
Dude, this thing is huge!
貌似上面还有芝士呢
I think it stiII has cheese on it.
~ 噢喂 ~
~ Ooh wee ~
~ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ~
~ La, Ia, Ia, Ia, Ia, IaIa ~
~ 当我步入派对 所有女孩都想知道 ~
~ When I step into the party aII the Iadies wanna know ~
~ 我会带着波霸 还是只秀我的黑人风 ~
~ I'm hangin' with the baIIers, yeah, or my nigga Ghost ~
~ 如果嫉妒者你想知道~
~ I can teII you what they say, haters~
~ 我可以告诉你她们在说什么 ~
~ if you wanna know ~
~ 她们说 噢喂 ~
~ They say ooh wee ~
~ 当我飚上我的奔驰车 所有女孩都想 ~
~ When I'm roIIin' my Mercedes aII the Iadies wanna roII ~
~ 做我的朱丽叶 而我就是你的罗密欧 ~
~ Be my JuIiet and I can be your Romeo ~
~ 如果你要惹麻烦 我就换个人 哈 ~
~ If you actin' menace I can pick another ho ~
~ 噢喂 噢喂 ~
~ Ooh wee, ooh wee ~
~ 噢喂 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ~
~ Ooh wee La, Ia, Ia, Ia, Ia, IaIa ~
~ 不论酷暑还是严冬 ~
~ In the middIe of the summer, or even 20 beIow ~
~ 我就是个无耻之徒 我就是这么酷 ~
~ I'm a bad motherfucker I'm way too fuckin' coId ~
~ 让我告诉你 当我秀出内裤时 ~
~ Let me teII you what they say when I'm puIIin' off my drawers ~
~ 她们说 噢喂 ~
~ They say ooh wee ~
~ 噢喂 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ~
~ Ooh wee La, Ia, Ia, Ia, Ia, IaIa ~
~ 噢喂 ~
~ Ooh wee ~
~ 哎哟 哎哟 ~
~ Aiyo, aiyo ~
~ 我来派对只是想好好玩 ~
~ My game's here to party just to cut up a rug ~
~ 别逼我做暴徒 ~
~ Don't make me have to cut up a thug ~
~ 来为我放点什么吧 DJ 因为这里只有爱 ~
~ Now pIay something for me, DJ, 'cause there's nothin' but Iove ~
~ 那些女孩们只是想找点乐子 ~
~ Hosted by the Iadies who Iookin' for somethin' to rub ~
~ 噢喂 ~
~ Ooh wee ~
伙计 天哪 我突然想到些事
Dude. Oh, my Go I just reaIized something.
什么?
What?
这么追着玛利亚到阿姆斯特丹
Maria's gonna think I'm a staIker, man.
她会认为我是跟踪狂的
I'm foIIowing her to Amsterdam.
伙计 放轻松
Dude, reIax.
我还参加过医学院的十分钟采访呢
I have a med schooI interview in ten minutes.
你也没见我崩溃啊
You don't see me freaking out.
别担心了 她会很高兴见到你的
Don't worry, man, she'II be psyched to see you.
高兴? 你觉得她会高兴吗?
Oh, psyched? You think she's gonna be psyched?
当然啦 伙计 她怎么会不高兴?
Totes, dude. Why wouIdn't she be?
那我们该怎么做?
So how does this work?
我们就…去阿姆斯特丹的各个旅馆
We justwe show up in Amsterdam and we start caIIing hoteIs...
然后挨个询问是否有叫玛利亚的房客?
and ask if they have a Maria staying there?
我连她姓什么都不知道      伙计 没事的
I don't even know her Iast name.         Dude, it's totaIIy cooI.
我们一定会找到她的
We're definiteIy gonna find her.
阿姆斯特丹很小的 才不会…
Amsterdam is a very smaII pIace. It's not gonna be
先生 请到这边来 我需要对您做个检查
Sir, I need you to step aside, pIease. Let me search you.
警报响了吗?      不 没有
Did I beep?         No, you didn't beep.
只是个随机的安全检查
Just a random security check.
到这边来好吗? 就是这儿
If you couId just step aside, pIease? Just over here.
随机的?      是的
Random, huh?         Yeah.
也就是说 和我的种族无关?
So this has nothing to do with my ethnicity?
卡玛 照他说的做吧
Kumar, just do what the guy says.
先生 我们机场安检人员的工作
Sir, it's our job as airport security...
就是检查是否有武器或违禁药物
to search for aII possibIe weapons or iIIegaI drugs.
所以就因为我的肤色
So just because of the coIor of my skin
你怀疑我身上有违禁药物?
you assume that I have drugs on me?
不 他只是…      你算老几? 种族歧视者?
No, he's         What are you, a racist?
种族歧视? 老兄 我是黑人
Racist? Dude, I'm bIack.
他是黑人 不是种族歧视者
He's bIack. He's not a racist.
拜托 伙计 你连棕色都算不上
PIease, dude, you're bareIy even brown.
不 他不是那个意思
No, he didn't mean that.
和我相比 你就是马修派瑞
Compared to me, you Iook Iike Matthew Perry.
你叫谁马修派瑞呢? 贱人
Hey, who you caIIing Matthew Perry, bitch?
我叫你呢 你这个长着张马修派瑞脸的贱人
I'm caIIing you Matthew Perry, you Matthew PerryIooking bitch!
不 这里没人是马修派瑞 没有!
No, there's nobody here who is Matthew Perry. No one!
这里出什么事了?
What is going on here?
长官 这位马修派瑞认为我身上有违禁药品
Sir, Matthew Perry over here thinks that I have iIIegaI narcotics on me...
就因为我是少数名族
because I'm a minority.
这是典型的种族歧视
This is textbook raciaI profiIing...
我打算上告到美国公民自由协会或者政府…
and I'd be more than happy to caII the ACLU or the government
不不不 很抱歉给您添麻烦了 先生
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Sorry for the inconvenience, sir.
您可以走了
You can move aIong.
很高兴听您这么说 再见 马修派瑞
I appreciate it. Thanks, Matt Perry.
嗨 你干嘛呢你?
Hey, what are you doing?
你这么问是什么意思? 他叫我马修派瑞
What do you mean, what am I doing? He caIIed me Matthew Perry.
你看上去确实挺像
WeII, you Iook Iike Matthew Perry.
他是白人!      那又如何?
He's white!         So what?
你为什么总是要不依不饶呢?
Why does everything have to become a huge argument with you, man?
因为这是在美国 伙计
'Cause this is America, dude...
既然我有言论自由的权利
and as Iong as I have my freedom of speech,
那就没人能让我闭嘴
no one's gonna shut me up.
卡玛?
Kumar?
罗迪?
RoIdy?
温妮莎      哦 天哪
Vanessa.         Oh, my God!
很高兴见到你      很高兴见到你们 我…
Good to see you.         So good to see you. I
嗨 嘿      嗨
Hi. Hey.         Hey.
嗨
Hey.
天哪 真是好久不见 你们这是去哪呢?
God, it's been forever. What are you guys doing?
我们正要去阿姆斯特丹
We're actuaIIy on our way to Amsterdam.
阿姆斯特丹?      是的
Amsterdam?         Yeah.
你们可是一点都没变
WeII, you guys haven't changed.
你可变漂亮了 你头发变得…
You have. You Iook amazing. Your hair is diff
她看上去很不错吧?      是的
Doesn't she Iook amazing?         Yeah.
是啊 你看上去真不错 漂亮多了
Yeah, you Iook great. You Iook awesome. Sorry.
简直无法形容 你变了而且…
What am I even saying? You Iook different and
卡玛派特 你又开始激动了      有那么点
Kumar PateI, you're fIustered.         LittIe bit.
那么你呢?
So, what's up with you?
还在和那个爱穿麋鹿牌的猥琐男约会?
You stiII dating the Abercrombiewearing douchebag?
其实 是布鲁克斯的兄弟
ActuaIIy, it's Brooks Brothers.
柯尔特! 最近过得如何? 兄弟
CoIton! How are you, buddy?
很高兴见到你      很高兴见到你
Good to see ya.         Good to see you.
我们不再约会了
And we're not dating anymore.
是因为 我们要结婚了
No. We...are getting married.
祝贺你们啊
CongratuIations, you guys.
你们要结婚了?      是的
You're fucking getting married?         Yeah.
什么时候?      下周
When?         Next week.
那将会是完美的一天
It's going to be a perfect day.
如果我们能拿到那些百合做花束的话
I mean, that's assuming we get those Stargazer IiIies for the bouquets.
那个花店可真是个噩梦
This fIorist has been a compIete nightmare.
真够混的
Fucking asshoIes.
婚礼基本上都是柯尔特一手包办的
CoIton's practicaIIy pIanning the whoIe wedding aII by himseIf.
罗迪 布鲁斯特居然会放你大假?
So, RoId, Brewster Keegan Ietting you off the Ieash for a IittIe vaycay?
现在由我掌管了 柯尔特
I own that pIace now, CoIton.
谢谢你的帮忙
Thank you so much for the hookup.
嗨 我在惠特克遇到过托德
Hey, I ran into Todd, at Whitaker's, of course.
他说你现在为政府工作
He toId me you got a job working for the government.
是的! 布什总统和我父亲以前在同一联谊会
Yeah! Yeah, President Bush and my dad were in the same fraternity.
哦 天哪      天哪
Oh, that's right.         Oh, Jesus.
是啊 他任命我爸爸就职国防部门
Yeah, yeah, when he gave my dad that appointment at the Defense Department...
我就成了他的副手      狗屎运
I became his righthand man.         Douche.
总统也许会来参加我们的婚礼
The President's supposed to be at our wedding...
不过你也知道他很忙的      是的
but you know how busy he is.         Yeah.
这工作太不可思议了 伙计
Sounds Iike an incredibIe job, man.
你接触的可都是上层啊
Hey, you reaIIy got some major connections to the top.
有事尽管开口
If you ever need anything, I'm your man.
太感激了      愿为你效劳
Thank you so much, buddy.         Anytime.
这家伙太牛了
This guy's the best.
宝贝 我们得走了      是的
So, sweetheart, we shouId get going.         Yes.
再次很荣幸能见到你们      再次恭喜你们
Good to see you guys again.         CongratuIations again.
谢谢 多保重      太好了
Thank you. Take care, thank you.         It's so nice.
再见      再见
Bye.         Bye.
伙计 真不敢相信他们要结婚了
Dude, I can't beIieve they're getting married.
我们才分手两年
We've onIy been broken up two years.
何况他还长了张强奸犯的脸
PIus that dude has daterape face.
我不懂你的意思
I don't even know what that is.
他看上去就像个流氓
One who possesses the face of a date rapist.
是啊 听着
Right. Listen...
我为你难过 兄弟
I'm sorry, bro.
但我们还是得去阿姆斯特丹 走吧
But we are going to Amsterdam. Come on.
是啊 是啊 罗迪
This is true. This is true, RoIdy.
~ 噢喂 ~
~ Ooh wee ~
这可真不像我啊      是啊
Man, this is so not Iike me.         Yeah.
就像是全新的哈罗德 更好更快更强
It's Iike I'm a whoIe new HaroId. Better, faster, stronger.
不错
Nice.
我以前可是连病假都没请过
Man, I've never used a sick day before.
现在却连请了一整个星期的假
I'm taking a whoIe week off from work here, man.
而且不到八小时 我们就要到阿姆斯特丹了
And in Iess than eight hours, we're gonna be in Amsterdam.
真是太疯狂了 太疯狂了      是的 伙计
This is nuts. This is nuts.         I know, dude.
就像《欧洲旅行》那样 不过没那么糟糕
It's gonna be exactIy Iike Euro TrIp, onIy it's not gonna suck.
一定会很彪悍的      一定一定会的
It's gonna be awesome.         It's not not gonna be awesome.
伙计 这小妞让我勃起了 太彪悍了
Dude. Dude, this chick's giving me such a boner, it's awesome.
谢谢 全被你毁了
Thank you. You ruined the moment.
她是你的了 伙计
She's aII yours, buddy.
要暂停吗?      我去下洗手间
You wanna pause it?         I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
不用了
No, that's
你尽情享用吧
Enjoy.
等等
Just a minute.
见鬼
Fuc
嗨 嗨
Hey, hey.
让我进来
Let me in.
你干嘛? 我在尿尿呢 混蛋
What are you doing? I'm taking a piss, asshoIe!
没事      哟!
Yeah.         Yo!
我可不想和你一起加入High上云霄俱乐部
I'm not joining the miIehigh cIub with you.
现实版的如何?
What about the reaIIy high cIub?
你智障啊?      不是
Are you retarded?         No.
你把大麻带上飞机了?
You brought weed on the fucking airpIane?
是的      你有病啊?
Yep.         What the fuck?
等等 那你还羞辱那个保安
Wait a second. You were giving that security guard shit.
是的 要不然我怎么能混上来?
Yeah. How eIse was I supposed to get past him?
比如别携带违禁药物?
By not bringing drugs on an airpIane?
你在做什么? 这是什么东西?      等着瞧
LookWhat are you doing? What is this?         You'II see.
哈罗德李 郑重地向你介绍一项我的发明
HaroId Lee, I wouId Iike to introduce you to an invention of mine.
无烟器
Meet the smokeIess bong.
你做的?      没错
You made this?         You know, I did.
当你在卖力工作的时候
When you were sIaving away at work...
我则热衷于我的社会生产实践
I was actuaIIy being a productive member of society.
是的 看着挺有意思
Yeah, that's reaIIy productive.
让我来展示给你看看
Let me show you how it works.
在这个洞上头放上一点
So you take a IittIe weed...
大麻然后就和普通水烟一样点燃
put it in the bowI right here and Iight it just Iike a normaI bong, OK?
最有才的部分到了
Now here's the truIy genius part.
在这个装置里面 我设计了一个很小的风扇
Inside this mechanism, I have actuaIIy made a IittIe tiny, tiny fan...
还有一些消毒粉末 这些可以看成是除臭剂
and some disinfectant powder, OK, it works sort of Iike a deodorizer...
就像来沙尔(消毒剂名)一样除去气味
so that anything it expunges smeIIs Iike LysoI.
把它放下      不 伙计
Put it away.         No, dude.
你就不能等我们到了阿姆斯特丹吗?
Can you not wait tiII we get to Amsterdam?
那里可是烟草王国!
It's the weed capitaI of the worId!
不      把这玩意放下
No.         Put the bong away!
来试下吧      不要!
Take the inauguraI hit, dude.         No!
来嘛 伙计
Come on, man.
把它放下 把这该死的玩意放下
Put it away. Put the frickin' bong away.
抱歉 抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Turb
恐怖分子!
Terrorist!
罗迪?
RoIdy?
他手上是什么鬼玩意?
What the fuck is that thing in his hands?
放心 女士 他不是恐怖分子
No, ma'am, not a terrorist.
他只是个白痴而已
He's just an idiot.
这只是根烟斗(听上去像炸弹的谐音)
This is just a bong.
他说那是个炸弹!
He said he got a bomb!
大家不要惊慌 那只是水烟而已
No, peopIe, it's a water pipe for tobacco.
不不不 这不是炸弹 是根烟斗
No, no, no, it's not a bomb. It's just a bong.
毒气!
Poison gas!
是大麻! 大麻!
It's marijuana! Marijuana!
你可挑错飞机了 你这该死的恐怖分子!
You picked the wrong pIane, you terrorist fuck!
嘿! 嘿 你干嘛呢?
Hey! Hey, what are you doing?
三位中将在飞机上呢 三位!
There are three air marshaIs on board. Three!
我们不是恐怖分子!
We are not terrorists!
先生 那个是烟斗 不是炸弹
Sir, that's a bong, not a bomb.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
我把这个搞定了!
I got this one!
罗迪?      求你不要!
RoIdy?         PIease don't!
我疼死了!
I am in a great amount of pain!
大家不要惊慌 请冷静 我们已控制了局面
Everybody reIax. Just caIm down. Everything is under controI.
请求返航 我们得把这俩混蛋遣送回美国
TeII 'em to turn the pIane around. These two asshoIes are goin' back to the U.S.
福克斯部长 感谢您的到来
Secretary Fox. GIad you couId make it.
我怎能错过这么严重的恐怖袭击呢?
Think I'd miss a terrorist attack of this magnitude?
绝不可能
Not a fuckin' chance.
他们是谁?
Who are these peopIe?
各个情报部门的代表
Representatives of the different inteIIigence agencies.
惠特莫尔部长也会到吧?
I assume Secretary Whitmore's coming?
不会 他正在冰川湾玩冰上垂钓
Negative. He's on an ice fishing trip in GIacier Bay.
他不在的时候由我掌管
I'm in charge whiIe he's gone.
难道没有人通知他么?
WeII, shouIdn't he be aIerted?
难道这件事不比冰上垂钓更重要吗?
Isn't this issue of more importance than an ice fishing trip?
你算哪根葱?
Who are you again?
约翰比彻博士 国家安全局副主席
Dr. John Beecher, Vice Chairman of the NSA.
是么 听着 笨蛋博士
Yeah, weII, Iisten, Dr...Dipshit.
显然你从来没玩过冰上垂钓
You've obviousIy never been ice fishing before.
是的 我没有
No, I haven't.
是的 所以你不知道这有多好玩
Yeah, weII, it's fucking exhiIarating.
而没人会希望在钓梭子鱼的时候被打扰
The Iast thing anyone wouId want whiIe fishing for pike is to be interrupted.
所以靠边站
Now back off...
我要开始做事了
and Iet me do my job.
那个眼神诡异的家伙是怎么了?
What's up with the guy with the weird eyes?
他是残废呢还是怎么了?
He handicapped or something?
我们觉得他有韩国血统
We beIieve he's of Korean descent.
上帝
My God.
北朝鲜和基地组织的合作
North Korea and aIQaeda workin' together.
比我想象中的更厉害
This is bigger than I thought.
你就不能等等吗?
You couIdn't wait?
就真那么急?
You couIdn't fucking wait?
我们将要去的阿姆斯特丹
We were about to have aII the IegaI weed we wanted.
你想要多少大麻就有多少!
You know, in Amsterdam, where we were going!
以为你们可以逍遥法外吗?
Thought you couId get away with this, huh?
911过后 你们都把国际安全当笑话了是吧?
You thought that after 9I11 our nationaI security was a joke, huh?
不过…
WeII...
你猜怎么着?
guess what?
怎么着?
What?
我们就知道你们这些混蛋会再来的
We knew you fuckers wouId be back.
见鬼了!      可是我们都是美国人 先生
HoIy shit!         But we're Americans, man.
我们爱美国!      爱得死去活来
We Iove America!         Very much.
在你们试图炸毁一架坐满美国人的飞机之后
That's a convenient thing to say...
说起这些话来还真溜啊
after you try and bIow up a pIane fiIIed with Americans!
不      不 我们没有
No.         No, we didn't do
不 你们搞错了
No, you see, you have the wrong idea.
我的白痴朋友带了大麻
My idiot friend here brought marijuana...
上飞机      嗨嗨嗨嗨
on the pIane.         Yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey.
闭嘴吧 凯蒂猫 我知道你们组织靠大麻维生
Zip it, HeIIo Kitty. OK? I know your operation's funded through drugs.
不 这是典型的官方调调 我…
No. This is typicaI government buIIshit, sir. I
嗨嗨嗨 闭嘴吧你      我…
Hey, hey, hey. Shut up. Shut up!         I
不 我正想解释呢! 哈罗德!      闭嘴!
No, I'm trying to expIain it! HaroId!         Shut up!
我们可以用下电话么?
Do we have the right to make a phone caII?
是的 当然!
Yeah. Yeah!
抱歉 你们现在想要人权了
I'm sorry. You want rights now.
你们想要自由
You want freedoms right now.
现在什么时候了? 是自由时间了么?
Is it time? Is it freedom o'cIock?
你猜怎么着?      怎么着?
Guess what.         What?
你们将要去的地方 没人听说过人权
Where you guys are going, they have never even heard of rights.
我们要去哪?
WeII, where are we going?
关塔那摩监狱 古巴 (美国关押政治犯的地方)
我们是无辜的! 我们是无辜的!
We're innocent men! We're innocent men!
我是无辜的
I'm an innocent man.
我献过血
I donate bIood.
还给孩子买过玩具
And toys for tots.
现在却在关塔那摩监狱
And now I'm in Guantanamo Bay.
知道我为什么反对纳税了吧?
See why I'm against paying taxes?
嗨!嗨
Hey! Hey.
操你妈的!
Fuck you!
伙计 冷静点 好吗?
Dude, caIm down, OK?
试着想想好的方面 这儿有洗脸盆有厕所
Look on the bright side. There's a sink. There's a toiIet.
枕头看起来也很舒服
The piIIow actuaIIy Iooks pretty comfortabIe.
行了 拜托你别再和我说话了
OK. You don't speak to me, ever.
永远      好吧
Ever.         OK.
不! 闭嘴!      好吧
No! Shut up!         OK.
你们怎么会被关进来的?
So what are you guys in here for?
为让美国人自食其果
For giving the United States a taste of their own medicine.
你们真的是恐怖分子?
You guys are reaI terrorists?
有些人是这么称呼我们
Some caII us terrorists.
但另一部分人叫我们英雄
Others caII us heroes.
得了吧 杀害无辜群众也算是英雄?
Screw that. You think you guys are heroes for kiIIing innocent peopIe?
就因为你们这群混蛋我们才会在这个鬼地方
It's 'cause of asshoIes Iike you that we're even in this fucking pIace...
你们这群懦夫!
you fucking cowards!
也许如果你们的人不再吃甜甜圈
WeII, maybe if the peopIe in your country stopped eating donuts...
而去多想想你们的国家对世界做了什么
and started reaIizing what your government is doing to the worId...
我们这样的混蛋就会消失了
asshoIes Iike us wouIdn't exist.
去死吧! 甜甜圈美味极了!      很好吃
Fuck you! Donuts are awesome!         They're deIicious.
你们喜欢吃甜甜圈?
You Iike donuts?
那等着看你们在这能吃到什么吧
WeII, wait tiII you see what they make you eat in here.
是么?      这儿提供什么吃的?
Yeah?         What do they make you eat in here?
我…
I
听说过”鸡鸡”三明治么?
Ever hear of a cockmeat sandwich?
这是什么玩意?
What's a cockmeat sandwich?
答案马上为您揭晓
You're about to find out.
马上 孬种
Right about now. Sucker.
“鸡鸡”三明治时间到 你懂规矩的
AII right, cockmeat sandwich time. You know the driII.
那他们呢? 他们是新来的!
What about them? They just got here!
大鲍勃会负责的
Big Bob's taking care of them.
大鲍勃      大鲍勃?
Big Bob.         Big Bob?
祝你们用餐愉快
I hope you Iike donuts.
我们工作去吧 嗨 听着 伙计 好好享受
Let's go to work. Hey, Iisten, guys, enjoy.
开眼了
HoIy shit.
噢 就这样
Oh, yeah, that's it.
这可不好      是的 卡玛 相当不好
This is not good.         No, Kumar, it is not good.
我从没吸过小鸡鸡      同上
I've never had to suck a dick before.         Me neither.
我猜它吸过
I bet it sucks dick.
他来了
Shit, dude.
千万不要是大鲍勃 千万不要是大鲍勃
PIease don't Iet it be Big Bob. PIease don't Iet it be Big Bob.
千万不要是大鲍勃 拜托
PIease don't Iet it be Big Bob. Come on.
千万不要是大鲍勃 千万不要是大鲍勃
PIease don't Iet it be Big Bob. PIease don't Iet it be Big Bob.
千万不要是大鲍勃
PIease don't Iet it be Big Bob.
千万不要是大鲍勃      大鲍勃来也
PIease don't Iet it be Big Bob.         I'm Big Bob.
操      当然是你啦
Fuck.         Yes, you are.
准备好品尝”鸡鸡”三明治了么?
You boys ready for your cockmeat sandwich?
还没?
No?
那你们最好马上变得如饥似渴
WeII, you better get hungry reaI fast...
因为这里有个巨大的三明治在等着你们
'cause I got a whoIe Iot of sandwich waitin' for ya.
妈逼诶!
HoIy shit!
好了 我们开始吧      等等 大鲍勃…
AII right, Iet's get goin'.         HoId on,Big Bob...
在这之前我想问个问题
I got to ask you a question before this aII goes down.
这里的警卫都是同志?      当然不是!
AII the guards in Guantanamo are gay?         Fuck, no!
这和是不是同志没半点关系!
Ain't nothing gay about getting your dick sucked!
你们才是吸我鸡鸡的同志!
You're the ones that's gay for suckin' my dick!
什么?      其实…
What?         In fact...
过会可别让我不爽
creeps me out just bein' around you fags.
可是…      好了
But         AII right.
等等…      跪下
Wait         Get down on your knees...
张嘴      求你了 大鲍勃
and open your mouths.         PIease, Big Bob.
要不踢我们屁股代替吧?
Why don't you just kick our ass instead?
跪下!      好吧 好吧
Get on your fucking knees!         AII right. AII right.
好好好好      你先来 伙计
AII right, aII right, aII right, aII right.         You go first, dude.
但愿你们喜欢额外的蛋黄酱
Hope you boys Iike extra mayo.
上帝啊 卡玛      我恨你!
Jesus, Kumar.         Oh, I hate you so much!
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
天哪 他的鸡鸡闻起来好像大便
God, his dick smeIIs Iike shit, dude.
我操!
HoIy shit!
发生什么事了?
What the heII happened?
这个恐怖分子咬我的鸡鸡!
That terrorist fuck bit my dick!
走吧      等等等 等一下
Come on.         Wait, wait, wait, wait a second!
我们该吗? 如果出去被杀了怎么办?
ShouId we? What if they kiII us out there?
不逃的话还得吸他们的鸡鸡
They're gonna fucking make us suck their dicks if we don't.
我们会死的 快走吧
We're gonna die in here. Come on.
妈的 妈的      哦 我靠 哦 我靠
Fuck. Fuck.         Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
我靠 我靠      妈的 妈的
Shit. Shit.         Fuck. Fuck.
哦 我靠! 快出去!      妈的!
Oh, shit! Get out!         Fuck!
哦 我靠 我靠
Oh, shit. Shit.
门 门在那儿
Door, door.
看 看 看
Look, Iook, Iook.
他在干嘛呢?
What the fuck is he doing?
我们快走! 快 快 快 快
We've got to go now, now, now, now, now!
闻起来就像烧焦的大便
It smeIIs Iike burnt asshoIe.
真他妈不敢相信
I can't fucking beIieve this.
我靠!
Fuck!
我手腕肿了!
My wrist is sweIIing, man!
闭嘴      我们会死在这丛林里的
Shut up.         We're gonna die in a jungIe!
闭嘴!      我靠!
Shut up!         Fuck!
小心印度豹! 这里是印度豹的天下!
Watch out for cheetahs! This is cheetah turf.
怎么了?      我靠
What?         OK. Fuck.
我们到海边了 现在怎么办?
We hit ocean. What do we do now?
好吧
AII right.
嗨 看 看那儿!
Hey, Iook, Iook!
请问
Excuse me.
你们这是去美国吗?
You guys going to America?
是的
Si, vamos.
我们要去的
Yes, we're going.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们走吧      好 好
Es mio.         Vamos, vamos.
乔治 我跟你说
I'm teIIing you, Jorge...
你到了美国第一件要做的事就是
the first thing you have to do when you get to America...
买一台数字录像机 懂吗?
buy a device caIIed TiVo, OK?
如果你是个守法的公民 自由对你毫无意义
Freedom means nothing if you're a sIave to reguIar programming...
我向你保证
I promise you that.
你现在在想什么呢?
And now, how about you focus?
我们应该考虑下到了美国该怎么办?
We gotta figure out what to do when we get to the States.
没钱没证件 什么都没有
We don't have waIIets. We don't have any ID. We've got nothing.
我认为我们该在迈阿密附近登陆 对吧?
WeII, I figure we're gonna Iand somewhere around Miami, right?
那里是我们唯一知道有朋友住的地方
There's onIy one guy we know who Iives down there.
你是说 罗扎      是的
Who do we know thatRaza.         Yeah.
我们得去找罗扎
We gotta go see Raza.
再见      一路顺风
AdIos.         Hasta Iuego.
谢谢      真是好人啊
Thanks again.         What nice peopIe.
伙计 我们到南佛罗里达了
Man, South FIorida here we are.
好吧 我们该怎么去找罗扎?
OK. So, now how do we get to Raza's?
最直接的方法就是走 我们走
The professionaI way. We waIk. Let's go.
走?      是的
WaIk?         Yeah.
我猜去罗扎那儿该…
So I guess Raza's
我们会找到的 会找到的      往那走
We'II find it, we'II find it.         ...thataway. Yeah.
~ 山谷 爸爸 ~
~ DaIe asi, papI ~
~ Tocame(西班牙语歌词) ~
~ Tocame ~
~ 哎呀 ~
~ Ay ~
~ 爸爸 ~
~ PapI ~
~ 哎呀 ~
~ Ay ~
~ 爸爸 ~
~ PapI ~
~ 哎呀 ~
~ Ay ~
罗扎的屋子可真不错
Wow, Raza's pIace is pretty sweet.
有点迈阿密犹太人区的感觉
Kinda ghetto for Miami.
你好      你好
Hi.         Hey.
你们不是因为噪声来抗议的吧?
Y'aII aren't here to compIain about the noise, are you?
不 我们不是来抗议噪音的
No. We're not... here to compIain about the noise.
我们…
We're
我们是来看看
We are here to see
他叫什么来着? 我们是来…      阴道
What is his name? We're here         Vagina.
我们是来找罗扎的
No, we're here to see Raza.
好的 跟我来吧
OK. FoIIow me.
谢谢你 女士
Thank you, ma'am.
我们还是跟着…你吧
We'II foIIow...you, I guess.
~ 她成功了 她成功了 ~
~ She got it, she got it ~
~ 她说 男孩 来吧 ~
~ She said, ''Boy, go ahead'' ~
~ 在我还没摸到之前 ~
~ As Iong as I don't touch it ~
~ 我说 我怎么可能想中断 ~
~ I said, ''Now, why the heII wouId I wanna interrupt it?'' ~
嗨
Hey.
你好爱国      谢谢
Very patriotic of you.         Thank you.
嗨 帅哥      嗨
Hey, guys.         Hey.
嗨 罗扎!      什么事?
Hey, Raza!         What?
什么风把你们吹来了?
What's up?
卡玛和罗迪?      最近过得如何?
Kumar and RoIdy?         What's up, man?
毕业后就再也没见过你们了
I haven't seen you guys since graduation.
你们怎么来这儿了?
What are you guys doing here?
等等 这些橙色跳伞服是怎么回事?
Wait, what's up with the orange jumpsuits?
嗨 不不 第一个问题是…
Hey, no, no, question number one
这个派对是怎么一回事?      你指什么?
...what's up with this party?         What do you mean?
裸露的阴道随处可见
There's exposed vagina aII over your house.
哦 那是我的主意
Yeah. That was my idea.
不知道你们如何 我痴迷于各种袒胸衣
I don't know about you guys, I'm sick of aII the hype over topIess.
真的? 我一直喜欢袒胸露乳
ReaIIy? I aIways Iiked topIessness. That's
这就是我      是么? 我现在尝试…
That's just me.         Yeah? WeII, I'm starting...
露下体的 所以 这是场露下体派对
the bottomIess trend. Hence, the bottomIess party.
你们怎么会来南部海滩的?
So what are you guys doing in South Beach?
为什么不由你来问? 我正想知道
How about you answer that question? I'm gonna go check this out.
你们要去哪?      嗨 伙计
Where are you going?         Bang bang, buddy.
听着 我们真的很抱歉来麻烦你
Listen. I'm reaIIy sorry to bother you with this.
你还好吧?      不好
You aII right?         Not reaIIy.
他们被关进去还不到一个小时 就跑掉了?
They were Iocked up for Iess than an hour, and they aIready escaped?
见鬼 确保别走漏风声给媒体
Damn it. Make sure the press doesn't get wind of this.
不能让公众觉得我们很无能
Don't need the pubIic thinking we're some twobit operation.
明白 长官
Got it, sir.
应该不是基地组织或者北朝鲜干的
It must have been either aIQaeda or North Korea who broke 'em up.
严密监视他们之间是否有任何联系
Find out if they have any reIatives in the country.
你早该这么做了
You probabIy shouId have done that in the first pIace.
你对我的指挥有意见 比彻?
Do you have a probIem with the way I'm running the show, Beecher?
我只是说…
I'm just saying that...
我看过哈罗德李和卡玛派特的资料
I've Iooked through the fiIes on HaroId Lee and Kumar PateI.
他们都是在新泽西长大的
They were both born and raised in New Jersey.
除了偶尔的逃票记录 他们是清白的
Other than a coupIe of traffic tickets, they're cIean.
对 所以他们才会越狱
Right. That's why they just broke out of prison.
但是 他们是不是该被关押在那还是个问题
But theyIt's not even cIear that they shouId have been there in the first pIace.
闭嘴
Shut your
看见这个可爱的白人小女孩没 比彻?
You see this cute, IittIe white girI, Beecher?
是的
Yeah.
难道你希望她被强暴和谋杀么?
Do you want her to get raped and murdered?
当然不
Of course not.
你确定? 因为这就代表美国
You sure? 'Cause this is America.
你想强暴美国么?      不
Do you want to rape America?         No.
那就别唧唧歪歪了
Then stop fucking with me.
这可是很严肃的事
This is serious.
她很可爱
She's adorabIe.
所以你们是逃出来的?
So you guys are fucking fugitives?
都是卡玛惹的事
It's just it's Kumar's fauIt.
如果我们能顺利逃走
If we get out of this...
我们继续做朋友的几率会相当…
the chances of us remaining friends is highIy...
相当…波霸 哇哦
highIyboobies. Yeah.
嗨 你在干嘛呢?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
快把它穿上 扣紧了
Put that back on. And keep it on.
抱歉      你当这是什么派对了?
Sorry.         Fuckin' party do you think this is?
你们在谈什么?
Yo. What are you guys taIking about?
罗迪把我也卷进来了
RoIdy was just Ietting me in on your situation.
是么?      谢谢你们带我一起玩
Yeah?         Thanks for getting me invoIved.
那我们以前为你圆谎你就不提了?
What about that fuckin' time we had to cover for you...
把你怎么抓到螃蟹的事对你女朋友撒谎
Iie to your exgirIfriend about how you got crabs?
你欠我们的 兄弟
You owe us, man.
那是 那是      怎么样?
Yeah, that's right.         What?
好吧 那都是陈芝麻烂谷子的事了
OK, that was a Iong time ago.
我喜欢螃蟹
I Iove crabs.
说到前女友
Speaking of exgirIfriends...
你不是快结婚了么?
isn't yours getting married or something?
为什么就我被蒙在鼓里?
How does everybody know about this except for me?
等等
Wait.
柯尔特! 柯尔特格雷厄姆能帮我们
CoIton! CoIton Graham can heIp us out.
不! 我才不要!      对啊!
No! Fuck that!         Yes!
毫无疑问 也只有他可以还你们声誉了
No doubt. If anyone couId cIear your names, it's him.
抱歉的说 那个猥琐男是不会帮我们的
No, I'm sorry. That dickweed is not heIping us.
等等 你有他联系方式吗?
Wait a second. Do you have his contact info?
没有了 不过他的婚礼
Not anymore. But the wedding
会在德克萨斯州翰威特的家乡举行
is at his famiIy's estate in Hewitt, Texas.
不过你们应该不想在这个时候
But you don't want to bother them when they're doing their whoIe...
去打扰人家的 对吧?
wedding thing, right?
那也许真的是我们最后的救命稻草了
You know, that actuaIIy might be our onIy hope.
妈的! 我们怎么过去呢?
Fuck! How do we get there?
不能去机场 我们被通缉了
We can't go to the airport. They're Iooking for us.
我可以借车给你们      真的?
I'II Ioan you one of my cars.         ReaIIy?
但是首先 好好享受这个派对的精华吧
But first...y'aII got to get in the spirit of the party.
你说的精华是指…      你说呢?
What do you mean, spirit of         What do you think I mean?
那么你呢?      我? 我正乐在其中
What about you?         Me? I've been in the spirit.
哦 天哪!      哦 神那 老兄!
Oh, God!         Oh, my God, dude!
额滴神那!
Oh, my God!
我爱你的老二 罗扎      是么?　来尝尝
Love your dickdo, Raza.         Yeah. Drink it in.
搞什么鬼?      看上去真像本拉登的胡子
What the fuck?         That Iooks Iike Osama bin Laden's beard.
对吧? 好了 孩子们
I know, right? AII right, boys.
轮到你们了 一起来摇摆吧
Your turn. Let 'em dangIe.
我们还是做吧      做吧
Let's just do it.         Bring it.
倒数三声?
Count of three?
一
One.
二 三
Two, three.
你老二太彪悍了!
Your cocks are awesome, man!
那简直都没了
That's not even necessary.
你能…      哦 我的老二
WouId you pIease         Oh, my dick!
~ 我的鸡鸡付出了整晚的代价 ~
~ My dick cost a Iatenight fee ~
~ 你的鸡鸡染上了艾滋 ~
~ Your dick got the HIV ~
~ 我的鸡鸡两场连映 ~
~ My dick pIays on the doubIe feature screen ~
~ 你的鸡鸡上了DVD ~
~ Your dick went straight to DVD ~
~ 我的鸡鸡大如桥 ~
~ My dick bigger than a bridge ~
~ 你的鸡鸡如幼童 ~
~ Your dick Iook Iike a IittIe kid's ~
~ 我的鸡鸡壮如马 气势如虹 ~
~ My dick Iarge Iike the Chargers, the whoIe team ~
~ 你的鸡鸡看上去还未成年 ~
~ Your shit Iook Iike you 14 ~
~ 我的鸡鸡被锁入笼 ~
~ My dick Iocked in a cage, right ~
~ 你的鸡鸡临阵退缩 ~
~ Your dick suffer from stage fright ~
~ 我的鸡鸡如此抢手 ~
~ My dick so hot it's stoIen ~
~ 你的鸡鸡却像加里科尔曼 ~
~ Your dick Iook Iike Gary CoIeman ~
~ 我的鸡鸡又粉又大 ~
~ My dick pink and big ~
这辆车太拉风了      是啊 好拉风
This car is frickin' sweet.         Yeah, yeah, it's sweet.
因为我们是逃亡者
'Cause we're fugitives.
却开着黄色敞篷宝马 穿得像个富家子弟
Driving a yeIIow convertibIe with the top down, dressed Iike asshoIes!
看 他有这个
Yo. Yo. Yo, Iook, he has one of these things.
你能把它放下么?      不能 这能联网
WouId you put that down?         No, you can hook up to the Internet.
你还可以玩手掌游戏!
You can pIay MIke Tyson's PunchOutII on it. King Hippo's going down.
把它放好 把它放好
Put that away. Put that away.
我真不敢相信这种时候你还能想着玩游戏
I can't beIieve you can even think about pIaying games at a time Iike this, man.
你没想过如果我们爸妈知道会怎样吗?
You reaIize what wouId happen if our parents found out about this?
你把我们儿子关进了关塔那摩监狱?
You have sent our sons to Guantanamo Bay?
你们太侮辱人了!
This is an outrage!
你们这些阿拉伯人以为混进了这和谐社会
You Arabs think you can just mix in with our peacefuI society...
我们就找不到你们了?
and we're not gonna find you, huh?
我不是阿拉伯人! 我是印度人!
I am not Arab! I am Indian!
听着 我来这儿可不是找你吵架的 懂吗?
Look, Chief. I'm not here to argue sebIantics with you, OK?
我是来拯救生命的
I'm here to save Iives.
问问李知不知道他儿子的恐怖行为
Ask the Lees what they know about their son's terrorist activity.
听着 我们已经做了四十多年的美国公民了
Look, we have been American citizens for over 40 years.
坦率地说 我觉得你们现在很无礼
Now, frankIy, I find this very offensive.
我从没听过这么古怪的方言
They're using some sort of diaIect I've never heard before.
但我很肯定他有提到跟无礼有关的事
But I'm pretty sure he said something about going on the offensive.
告诉他们 我们知道他儿子的事…
TeII them we know what their son is up to...
如果不愿意合作 他将被判死刑
and if they don't cooperate, he couId be sentenced to death.
就这么说
Hit 'em. Yeah.
我们知道他在说什么!
We know what he said!
先生 哈罗德和卡玛都是好孩子
Sir, HaroId and Kumar are good boys.
我可是很优秀的翻译
I'm a pretty good transIator.
他们完全在胡言乱语
It's totaI gibberish.
他们这是在转移视线
They may be trying to stonewaII us.
你确定你说的是韩语 杰克?
Are you sure you speak Korean, Jack?
你懂韩语?
You speak Korean?
你不是在忽悠我吧?
You're not fucking with Daddy, are you?
你有韩国传统文学学位么?
Do you have a masters in romantic Korean Iiterature?
我有
Because I do...
而我觉得被冒犯了
and I'm offended.
我受够了
Good enough for me.
听着 抱歉
Look, excuse me...
我们不是有意要毁谤你们的儿子
we're not Iooking to hurt your sons...
我们只是想了解他们的行踪
we just wanna know where they are.
你们知道他们有佛罗里达的朋友吗?
Do you know if they know anybody in FIorida?
他们的朋友罗扎赛德住在迈阿密
Their friend Raza Syed Iives in Miami.
但他们为什么会在那?
But why wouId they be there?
他应该在医学院上学才是
He's supposed to be in medicaI schooI.
他们应该在监狱! 那才是恐怖分子的归属!
They are supposed to be in prison! That is where terrorists beIong!
他们的结局只有两种
These fuckers are goin' down.
死或是活
Dead. Or aIive.
用你那拙劣的粤语告诉他们
TeII them that in your fake chingchong Ianguage.
闭嘴! 你这个蠢货
Shut up! You're an idiot.
我不知道你们在说什么 伙计
I don't know what you're saying, buddy...
操你妈的
but fuck you.
操我妈的?      你怎能让他这么跟你说话?
Fuck me?         WiII you Iet him taIk to you Iike that?
听着 不 坐下      操我妈的?
Listen, no, sit down.         Fuck me?
嗨 看啊 我们到阿拉巴马了
Hey, Iook, man, we're in AIabama.
哇哦 这可是我们第一次到南部观光哈
Wow, we actuaIIy get a firsthand Iook at the South, huh?
嗨 我们可不是来南部观光的 对吧?
Hey, this wasn't supposed to be a trip through the South, OK?
这本该是我人生中最浪漫的一周
This was supposed to be the most romantic week of my Iife.
还记得吗? 就在你挑起事端之前 还记得吧?
Remember that? Before you fucked it up? You remember that?
冷静点 好吗? 我们会度过难关的
Just chiII, OK? We'II be out of this situation.
你马上就能把玛利亚拥入怀中了 不是么?
You'II be up in Maria's guts in no time, aII right?
嗨 她可不是什么随便的人
Hey. She's not some skank, man.
我以前从没对别人有过这种感觉 真的
I've never feIt this way about anyone before, reaIIy.
见鬼 我干嘛要和你说这些?
What the fuck? Why am I taIking to you about this?
说给你听你也不会懂
It's not Iike you wouId understand, so
~ 我要快乐 ~
~ I want to be happy ~
~ 我要快乐 就像… ~
~ I want to be happy, just Iike ~
抱歉 能关掉吗? 这里可是图书馆
Excuse me, pIease. WiII you turn that off? This is a Iibrary.
真他妈见鬼
What a fucking chode.
谢谢 下次再来哦!
Thank you, come again!
怎么回事?      我的老天
What the fuck?!         Oh, my God.
所有来单独隔间的人都是为了…
You know, the whoIe reason peopIe come to the stacks...
寻求和平和
is for some peace and...
安静
quiet.
我知道 很抱歉 我讨厌有人打扰我
Look, I know, I'm sorry. I hate it when peopIe disturb me here too.
只是这些微积分学把我整疯了
It's just this fucking caIcuIus finaI is kiIIing me.
我来帮你看看如何?      好啊
Do you mind if I take a Iook?         No.
你快做出来了 我可以吗?      当然
You're actuaIIy very cIose. May I?         Yeah.
请让一下
Excuse me.
我碰到你胸部了
I touched your breast.
没关系      抱歉
It's OK.         Sorry.
只要这样
You just go
哇哦 你很有才嘛
Wow. You're good at this.
谢谢
Thanks.
你高中时就学过微积分么?
What did you, Iike, take caIcuIus in high schooI or something?
其实 六年级的时候 我爸爸就教我了
ActuaIIy, my dad taught it to me in sixth grade.
莫非你是"天才小医生"?
What, are you Iike Doogie Howser?
不 那是不可能的 他是我偶像
No. AIthough that wouId be incredibIe. He's my hero.
我很喜欢那部片子
I Iove that show.
你在做什么呢?
What are you working on there?
是我创意写作课要交的一首诗
This is just a poem for my creative writing cIass.
就像
It's Iike
"三的平方根"?      不 不 抱歉
''The Square Root Of Three''?         No, no, I'm sorry
"卡玛派特爱的宣言"      还给我吧
''A poem of Iove by Kumar PateI.''         I need this.
嗨 我来念念嘛      不 不要
Hey, Iet me read it.         No, no.
为什么?      因为我还没写完
Why?         Because it's Iame.
那你来读给我听吧
Then read it to me.
我可不想你用那样的眼光看我
There's no way I'm Ietting you see me in that Iight.
好好做你的微积分吧
Good Iuck with your caIcuIus.
得了 害羞什么呀
Come on, don't be embarrassed.
很多女孩都觉得聪明是很性感的哦
You know, a Iot of girIs find inteIIigence sexy.
听着 我都不打算把这个给我教授看
Look, I'm not even gonna be showing this to my professor, aII right?
所以我现在才很有压力
That's why I'm so stressed out right now.
有压力?
Stressed out, huh?
跟我来
Come with me.
去哪?      来吧
...going?         Come on.
怎么了?
What?
你在图书馆吸毒? 被人捉到怎么办?
You're smoking drugs in the Iibrary? What if somebody catches us?
别担心 我会让你好好放松的
Don't worry. It'II heIp you reIax.
哦 小子
Oh, boy.
这是违法的
It's iIIegaI.
~ 我希望你和我一同垂钓 ~
~ I want your fish right by me ~
~ 就像应该的那样 ~
~ That's how it has to be ~
来吧
Here.
这样的话你会感觉很好
~copacetic if you Iet it so set up ~
~ 顺流而下 逆流而上 ~
~ And keep the downstream down and the upstream up ~
这是毒药
This is poison.
~ 我的史东妮 我的宝贝 ~
~ My stoney, my baby ~
我来教你
Let me heIp you.
~ 去它的口哨声 ~
~ Funk the groovin' thang whistIin' ~
~ 就像我的节奏那样 ~
~ As I rip my rhymes ~
~ 一次次地在夏日里款款而行 ~
~ Time and time again struttin' and in the summertime ~
~ 脱下它吧 做一个平民 ~
~ So screw it, strip down and be generic ~
~ 脱下它吧 做一个路人~
~ Strip down and be a passenger~
~脱下它吧 做一个信使 ~
~ Strip down and be a messenger ~
~ 问我 为什么在冬天我来到这世上 ~
~ In askin' why I'm born I come up bIank in the winter ~
~ 问我 为什么在上她的时候来到这世上 ~
~ In askin' why I'm born I come up on when I'm on her ~
~ 让时间回答 我的夏天 他的夏天 ~
~ It's time to find the kind My summer, his summer ~
我叫卡玛
I'm Kumar.
温妮莎
Vanessa.
你还没读那首诗呢
You're stiII not reading that poem.
~ 然后我亲了我的史东妮宝贝 ~
~ And then I kiss my stoney baby ~
~ 我的史东妮 史东妮 ~
~ My stoney, my stoney ~
~ 我的史东妮宝贝 ~
~ My stoney baby ~
~ 我的史东妮 ~
~ My stoney ~
~ 我的史东妮宝贝 ~
~ My stoney baby ~
卡玛
Kumar.
~ 我的史东妮宝贝 ~
~ My stoney baby ~
卡玛
Kumar.
卡玛 卡玛
Kumar. Kumar.
卡玛      是
Kumar.         Yeah.
怎么回事? 我们到阿拉巴马的伯明翰了
What's going on? We're in Birmingham, AIabama.
我们该来这儿的吗?
Are we supposed to be here?
怎么回事?
What's going on?
伙计 你干嘛把我们带这儿来?
Why did you bring us here, dude?
你什么意思?
What do you mean, why did I
你说这话什么意思? 是你负责指路的
You were supposed to be foIIowing the directions, asshoIe. What do you mean?
不是应该有个公路什么的吗?
There's got to be Iike a highway or something, right?
是的 应该有条公路
Yeah, there's got to be a highway.
前面怎么了?
What's going on up there?
~ 行动起来吧 ~
~ Squad up ~
~ 黑鬼们 ~
~ My niggas ~
~ 我看见了一些黑人女孩 ~
~ I see some pussyass niggas, so what the fuck ~
这是什么?
What the heII is this?
~ 我们打败了那些黑鬼 ~
~ We knock these niggas out ~
~ 我看见了些黑人女孩 你跃跃欲试了吗? ~
~ I see some pussyass niggas, so what the fuck you wanna do? ~
我还是掉头吧      直接过去嘛
I'm turning around.         Nah, just go through, man.
伙计 我们不能破坏人家比赛
Dude, we're not driving through this basketbaII game.
罗迪 我认为你比他们强大多了
You know, RoIdy, I reaIIy thought you were bigger than this.
伙计 我不是怕了他们是黑人
Dude, I'm not scared 'cause they're bIack.
而是他们的亢奋很吓人
I'm scared because they're scary.
这里可没有格雷戈里海因斯(节奏踢踏舞王)
And it's not Iike we got Gregory Hines out there.
他们没这么可怕
They're not that scary.
我的球!
It's my baII!
掉头
Turn around.
~ 抢劫那个混蛋吧 把他扔进臭水沟 ~
~ Rob this motherfucker, drop his punk ass in a ditch ~
~ 拖上那个黑女孩 狠狠揍她的屁股 ~
~ Drag this pussy nigga, sIap his ass up Iike a bitch ~
~ 我的黑人就是我的 因为我的 ~
~ My niggas is my niggas 'cause my niggas ~
妈的! 动不了了!      我靠!
Fuck! It won't move!         Shit, dude.
~ 射向他的嘴唇 ~
~ Shoot him dead between his Iips ~
~ 我看到几个女孩 ~
~ I see some pussy ~
糟了    音乐声没了
That's not good.         Now there's no music, man.
死翘翘了
Shit, man.
妈的!      我的乔丹 黑鬼!
Motherfucker!         My Jordans, nigga!
完了      完了 完了
Shit, this isn't good.         This is not good. This is not good.
不 不 不
No. No. No.
他们来了
They're coming over here.
他妈的 你没长眼睛啊?
Fucking shit. Why did you do that?
对啊 我故意撞坏消防栓的
Yeah, I hit a fire hydrant on purpose.
他们操家伙了
They're getting weapons, man.
我们怎么办? 我们怎么办啊?
AII right, what do we do? What do we do?
跑 跑 跑
Run, run, run. Run, run.
你们去哪? 见鬼!      我们是来帮忙的
Where y'aII going? Damn!         We was just trying to heIp.
有人去报警么 我们要举报
Man, somebody caII the poIice. We need to report this.
你喜欢那辆车吗?      去死吧你
Yeah, that's right. You Iike the ride?         Fuck you, man.
他们昨晚弃车而逃了
They abandoned it Iast night.
车主是一个叫罗扎赛德的
It's registered to a Raza Syed.
目击者提供的司机和乘客特征
The witnesses' description of the driver and passenger...
符合李和派特
match that of Lee and PateI.
昨晚我们企图逮捕罗扎赛德
We tried bringing in Syed Iast night
但他已经离开这个国家了
but he's aIready Ieft the country.
我们已经很接近他们了
WeII, they know we're cIosing in on 'em, that's why.
好的 不 我会给你回电的 好的
OK. No, I'II give you a caII. AII right.
不 不 不 不!
No, no, no, no!
见鬼      放松 放松
HoIy shit!         Easy, easy!
放松      放松
Easy.         Easy!
这是我们的目击证人
This is our witness.
放下! 放下!
Put it down! Yo, put it down!
你们知道我有枪的!
You aII know I got one!
我也有!
I got one too!
你见到逃亡者了 对吧?
So, you saw the fugitives, huh?
是的 我已经告诉过治安官了
Yeah. It was Iike I was teIIing the Sheriff
对啊 我怎么知道你说的是不是真话?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. How do I know you're teIIing the truth?
我何必骗你呢 先生
I don't have a reason to Iie to you, man.
真的?
ReaIIy?
我向你保证 长官      我们走着瞧
Get up in your face, man.         We'II see.
错了
That ain't right.
他去哪?
Where's he going?
这怎么解释?
What's going on?
哦 不!
HeII no!
还是坦白从宽吧?
Now why don't you teII me what reaIIy happened?
那不是葡萄汽水么?
Is that grape soda?
怎么了?
What the fuck, yo?
好吧      继续 继续 继续
AII right.         HoId on, hoId on, hoId on!
太无知了
This is so ignorant.
对吧?      是的
ReaIIy?         Yes.
无知么?
Is this ignorant?
他是个种族歧视者 兄弟 他有种族歧视
Yo, that's racist, man. That's racist.
嗨 乔恩 你就看着他这么羞辱你?
Hey, Jon, are you gonna Iet him do that?
看看他有没有"酷爱"(饮料名)
See if he got KooIAid.
快没了 目击者
AImost gone, witness.
确定你没有要说的?
Sure there's not something you wanna teII me?
你开口之前我是不会停下的!
I'm not stoppin' untiI you crack!
我说过了 他们跑了!
I aIready toId you that they took off runnin'!
好吧 好吧
AII right, aII right, aII right.
别这样了 怀特先生已经都说了
This isn't necessary! Mr. White is teIIing you the truth!
你怎么就这么肯定啊 比彻?
Yeah, and how can you be so sure, Beecher?
看在上帝的份上 他没有任何不良记录
'Cause he doesn't have a poIice record.
他是个牙医罢了
He's an orthodontist, for Christ's sake.
那好吧 比彻
OK, then, Beech.
你觉得我们该怎么抓到那些恐怖分子呢?
How do you propose we find the terrorists, huh?
控制台有一部诺基亚7710被拿走了
There was a Nokia 77 10 taken from the consoIe.
我们有它的跟踪号码
We have its tracking numbers.
就我们说话这会儿卫星已经开始追踪了
Our sateIIites are running a trace on it, as we speak.
"酷爱"的事我可是认真的
I'm serious about that KooIAid.
发生什么事了?你在哪呢?
What's going on? Where are you?
伙计　说来话长
Dude, that is a fucking Iong story.
我们在阿拉巴马呢 正要去德克萨斯
We're actuaIIy in AIabama right now, heading to Texas.
什么声音? 你又在手淫? 你干嘛呢?
What is that sound? Are you jerking off again? What are you doing?
我正华丽滴尿尿呢
I'm taking a gIorious peepee.
嗨 听着 你们一定想不到
Hey, Iisten, you're not gonna beIieve this...
前几天晚上 参加完一个亚洲聚会后
but the other night, I ended up at that Asian party...
我操了辛迪金
and I schtupped Cindy Kim.
闭上你的脏嘴吧 你开玩笑吧?
Shut the fuck up. Are you serious?
没说笑 她回应了我一个美妙的高潮
Yeah, man, she even gave me a bIumpkin.
什么高潮?
What is a bIumpkin?
就是你边拉屎边做爱
It's when a girI gives you head whiIe you're sitting on the toiIet takin' a shit.
真的?
ReaIIy?
喂?      嗨 嗨! 你干嘛啊?
HeIIo?         Hey. Hey! What are you doing?
嗨? 说话啊?
HeIIo? Come, come?
完了吗?
Did you go?
哦 是的
Yeah, I'm done.
你答应过我们要好好比划比划的
You said to me we were gonna cross swords. You promised.
抱歉 小甜心
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
政府在搜寻我们的时候你还敢用手机?
Are you taIking on a ceIIphone when the government is Iooking for us?
伙计 是古德思丁罢了
Dude, it was just GoIdstein.
我有重要的事要跟他说
I had something important to teII him.
原来如此 很好
It's 'cause you had something That's good, that's OK.
现在 没有比想办法去德克萨斯更重要的了
Nothing is more important than finding a way to get to Texas.
懂吗?      明白
Do you get it?         Yes.
我们已经走了一整天了还没看到一条路
We've been waIking an entire day and we have not seen a street sign.
你明白不?
Do you get it?
我想说…      又来了 不
Can I say         Again. This isI can't.
伙计 坦率地说
Dude, honestIy...
你应该乐观一点啊!
you've got to be a IittIe more positive about these things, aII right?
乐观什么?
Positive about what? I don't
首先 欣赏下这阿拉巴马这美丽的风景
First of aII, Iook at this beautifuI AIabama Iandscape, OK?
你在新泽西可看不到这个
You don't get shit Iike this in New Jersey.
上帝啊 你…
God, you
嗨 伙计 看那
Hey, Iook, dude.
是一头幼鹿
It's a baby deer.
哇哦      天啊
Wow. Man.         Shit.
嗨 嗨
Hey. Hey.
看这头小鹿多漂亮
Look how cute this deer is, dude.
新泽西的根本没法和它比
Not Iike those asshoIe deer in New Jersey.
我知道
I know, man.
嗨 小家伙      伙计 阿拉巴马真不错
Hey, buddy.         Dude, AIabama's awesome.
他喜欢你
He Iikes you.
哦 天哪! 不!
Oh, my God!No!
很抱歉 这是我的地盘
Sorry about that. I was in my zone.
你们穿得这么滑稽在这干嘛呢?
What the heII are y'aII doing out here in them fancy cIothes?
我们正想去德克萨斯 但是迷路了
We were on our way to Texas and we got Iost.
德克萨斯?
Texas?
这离德克萨斯好远呢
You're a Iong way from Texas.
不!
No!
04年生的
Born in '04.
进去吧
Get in here.
哦 太阳快要落山了
Yeah. The sun's about to go down.
你们要找地方过夜么? 你们饿不?
Y'aII need a pIace to stay? Ya hungry?
是的 当然
Yeah, sure.
跟我来吧?
You want to foIIow me?
来吧
Come on.
也许我们不该去
Maybe we shouIdn't.
它已经死了 需要来点掌声么?
It's aIready dead. You need a hand, dude?
1902年的时候我祖父买下了这座岛
My grandpappy bought this Iand in 1902.
真不错啊
Very nice, sir.
这个地方真烂
This pIace is gonna suck.
亲爱的 我回来啦
Honey, I'm home.
我在这呢
I'm in here.
你该早点告诉我会带客人回来的
I wish you'da toId me you was bringing guests home.
那我会把家里打扫一下
I'da straightened up in here.
伙计们 这是我太太瑞蕾
FeIIas, this is my wife RayIene.
瑞蕾 这是哈罗德和卡玛
RayIene, meet HaroId and Kumar.
你好
HeIIo.
别握手了 我身上都是鹿血呢
Can't shake. I've just got...deer head aII over me.
见到你很高兴      我也是 男士们
Nice to meet you.         Nice to meet you boys.
不用拘束 随意好了      谢谢
You just make yourseIves at home.         Thank you.
亲爱的 数字用户环线出问题了
Honey, something's wrong with that DSL.
每次我上网 都显示”寻找服务器中”
Every time I go on the onIine, it says, ''Searching for server.''
你有没有试过与机场连接断开?
You try unpIugging the AirPort base?
我试过了 可还是没用
Yeah, I done did that but it didn't work.
你上网打算做什么呢?
What you need to go onIine fors, anyways?
我想要个新的卫星手提声音机
I was gonna get one of them new portabIe sateIIite radios.
你要卫星收音机做什么?
What the fuck you need a sateIIite radio for?
有客人在的时候不要这么凶巴巴的
Don't you be cussin' when we got company over.
伙计们      请无视我们的存在
Guys.         PIease don't worry about us.
我们经常斗嘴
We cuss aII the time.
你以为你算老几啊 敢打我?
Who do you think you is, hitting me?
你忘了你的普拉达包是谁买的了吗?
Who do you think bought you that Prada bag?
我说了我要的是古奇
I toId you I wanted a Gucci one.
古奇的更贵!
The Gucci bag cost more!
简的丈夫就买得起
WeII, Jan Sapperstein's husband sure couId afford it.
又把简扯上了
Here we go again with Jan Sapperstein.
我才不管她有什么
I don't give a rat's ass what that bitch got.
你还是安于现状吧
You be happy with what you have.
我有的只不过是一个猪狗不如的丈夫!
What I have is a husband who ain't worth a turd!
你这是在侮辱我?
You wanna give me shit now?
是的!      好吧 你去买吧!
That's right!         After everything I Iet you buy!
看看你的信用卡账单
Even Iook at the credit card biIIs?
你买?不觉得我们该换套高尔夫球了么?
...you buy?! Do you think we need another set of goIf baIIs?
更糟的是那些信用卡…
Even worse is the credit card miIes.
伙计们 我们先闪开一会
Guys, we're just gonna get out of here.
别这样 别傻了 你们是我们的客人
Nonsense. Don't be siIIy. You're our guests.
你们得留下吃饭
You guys have got to stay for supper.
不 我们不行啊      不了 谢谢 真的不行
No, we couIdn't. That's         No, thank you. We reaIIy couIdn't
当然 我们得先热热身
Of course, we're gonna have to get high first.
我们近了
We're cIose.
真是长见识了 我不知道农夫也吸烟
This is news to me. I never knew farmers smoked weed.
你一直以为我们不会这样? 那你就大错特错
You ever tried farmin' not high? It's borin' as shit.
这是很棒的事情
You know, this is great, guys.
我还以为
I kind of aIways, you know, sort of assumed...
南部的人民
that peopIe from the South were kinda
都是乡下人?
A bunch of dumb rednecks?
不      不不不 不是这样的
No.         No, no, no, no, no, no, no. That's not
客人来的时候 我们都把自己
We do try to keep our inbred son
近亲而生的儿子藏在地下室
in the basement when we have company.
伙计们 我不是这个意思 我只是
Guys, I didn't mean it Iike that. I was just
看他们那样儿!
Look at their faces!
妈的!
Fuck, fuck!
靠 他们找到我们了 他们找到我们了
Shit, they found us. They found us. They found us.
他们找到我们了 什么意思?
What do you mean, they found you?
你们惹什么麻烦了?
Are you boys in some kind of troubIe?
是的 这听起来很疯狂 但是…
AII right. This is gonna sound crazy, but, basicaIIy...
当时我们在去阿姆斯特丹的飞机上
we were on a pIane to Amsterdam...
我们被误认为是恐怖分子
and we got mistaken for terrorists
然后被带到了关塔那摩监狱
and we got sent to Guantanamo Bay...
然后我们逃了出来 随群古巴人偷渡到美国
and then we escaped and snuck into America with a bunch of Cubans...
我们现在正想去德克萨斯
and now we're trying to get to Texas...
那里有个人可以帮我们
where there's a guy who can heIp us out...
而那个人将要和卡玛的前女友结婚
and he's getting married to Kumar's exgirIfriend.
是这么回事
Yes.
好吧 真酷
OK. That's cooI.
我明白了      你确定
I understand that.         You do?
就像之前政府对待我们那样 知道吗?
Like the government's never screwed us over before. You know what?
你们藏到地下室去 其他的交给我来处理
Y'aII come down here and hide in the basement. I wiII handIe this.
谢谢 谢谢你们两位
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you, both.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
这里一点都不阴森嘛
OK. This isn't creepy.
那是什么?
What the heII is that?
你要冲着那诡异音乐去了?
You're waIking towards the creepy music?
回…
Ge
这首歌真不错 伙计
This song rocks, dude.
卡玛
Kumar.
这里有个印着小丑的火柴盒
Hey, dude, there's a Iighter here with a cIown on it.
上帝 怪物!
Jesus Christ, there's a fucking monster!
苍天啊!
God!
嗨 你身上有巧克力吗?
Hey, you don't happen to have a Baby Ruth on you, do you?
没有 你要这干嘛?
No. Why do you need a Baby Ruth?
这就是恰克赢斯洛斯的秘诀
That's how Chunk won over SIoth in The GoonIes.
这玩意看起来像斯洛斯?
This thing Iooks Iike SIoth?
我仿佛看到了动物的手
AII I saw was the creature's hand.
那手看起来像斯洛斯?
The hand Iooks Iike SIoth?
那是只怪物的手 就像只爪子
The fucking hand of an eviI monster, dude. Like fucking cIaws and shit.
我靠
Shit.
听着 不管发生什么
Listen, no matter what
都别让那动物知道它很丑 如何?
don't Iet the creature know that it's ugIy, OK?
我们绝不能批判它  让它觉察出异常
The Iast thing that we want to do is criticize it or make it feeI different...
因为它生来就带着可怕的残疾
just because it was born with horribIe deformities.
别担心 我来处理 他们是我的邻居
Don't worry. I got rid of 'em. It was just my neighbors.
那里有个可怕的独眼巨人
There's a fricking CycIops
在你的地下室      一个怪兽 伙计
...in your basement, man!         ...a fucking thing, dude!
你见到的是塞勒斯
You met Cyrus.
塞勒斯      你给它起的名字?
Cyrus.         You named it?
他是我们的儿子
Our son.
一定是你们把他吵醒了
You must have woke him up.
他应该在睡觉了 不好意思
He was supposed to be asIeep. I'm sorry.
你说地下室藏着近亲而生的儿子的时候
I thought you were joking...
我以为是开玩笑的
when you said you had an inbred son who Iives in your basement.
哦 这不是说笑
WeII, it ain't a joke.
瑞蕾和我是近亲 不过我们还是结婚了
RayIene and I here are sibIings, and we get it on.
但这并不表示我们就是有罪的
But that don't mean we ought to be judged.
你们现在一定很累了吧
You boys must be awfuI tired after what you've been through.
跟我来吧 带你们去卧室
Come with me, I'II show you to your bed.
你继续睡吧 孩子!
You better go back to sIeep, boy!
别让我下来哄你睡觉
Don't make me come down there and whip your CycIops ass!
棍棒底下出孝子
It's tough Iove.
这是最好的方式了
It's the best way.
我也不知道怎么会去和柯尔特约会的
I don't know what I was thinking dating that douchebag CoIton.
他是个流氓 你觉得呢?
He is a douchebag. What were you thinking?
和他做爱还得假装高潮真痛苦
But it was agony pretending his puny, IittIe penis satisfied me.
我打赌你一定想和我干了 对吧?
I bet. I bet you've been missing the thundercock too, haven't you, baby?
是的      真的?
Yeah.         Yeah?
你很想我?
Yeah, you've been missing it?
有多想?
How much?
很想很想      我敢打赌
A Iot.         I bet.
我一直在幻想      什么?
I kind of have this fantasy.         What is it?
如果这时候床上再多出一个人来该有多酷
I thought it'd be kinda cooI to bring somebody eIse in bed with us.
谁?
Who?
嗨 宝贝
Hey, baby.
哇哦!      如何?
Yeah!         Yeah?
她够火辣的吧?
She's hot, right?
我们来吧
Let's do it.
~关于这个女孩~
~ There's something About that woman ~
~她有让你欲罢不能的地方~
~ She's got something you can't Iive without ~
~让你心跳~
~ Makes your heart sing ~
快点 维迪
Faster, Weedy.
~关于这个女孩~
~ Something about that woman ~
~如果你怀疑你就会失去~
~ If you're in doubt then you are missing out ~
~一件好东西~
~ On a good thing ~
~我该放弃了~
~ I got to give it up ~
牙齿 牙齿 维迪 牙齿
Teeth, teeth, Weedy, teeth.
维迪!      怎么了?
Weedy!         Yeah?
哦!      你喜欢吗?
Yeah!         You Iike that?
放到屁股上去 维迪
Putting it in the ass now, Weedy.
感觉如何?
Yeah, how about that?
~ 关于这个女孩 ~
~ Something about that woman ~
~ 她有让你欲罢不能的地方 ~
~ She's got something you can't Iive without ~
~ 让你心跳 ~
~ Makes your heart sing ~
~ 关于这个女孩 ~
~ It's just something about that woman ~
~ 如果你怀疑你就会失去 ~
~ If you're in doubt then you are missing out ~
~ 一件好东西 ~
~ On a good thing ~
~ 我该放弃了 ~
~ I got to give it up ~
哇哦
Wow.
伙计
Dude.
我做了个最混乱的噩梦
I just had the most fuckedup nightmare.
得了吧 都是你 扰了我的春梦
Come on, man. I was having a reaIIy hot dream.
继续睡吧 伙计
Go back to bed, pIease, dude.
我们干嘛要走? 那个智障孩子挺可爱的
Why did we have to Ieave? Their GoonIes chiId was kind of cute.
我才不管呢 他来攻击我了
I don't care. It tried to fucking bite me.
上帝 我们每到一处
Jesus, every time the two of us try to get anywhere...
灾难就滚滚而来
it's fucking disaster after fucking disaster.
上帝 伙计 你真该来一口
Jesus, dude. Here, you reaIIy need a hit of this.
我可不想抽!
Dude, I don't want a fucking hit!
这就是你解决问题的方式 知道吗?
It's your soIution to everything, you know that?
好好想想 我们得尽快找到柯尔特
Think about it. We shouId be at CoIton's aIready.
又来了 我们还有两天时间去破坏婚礼呢
Hey, chiII, we stiII have two days to fuck up the wedding.
什么?      怎么了?
What?         What?
怎么了?      什么?
你想的就是这个对不? 去破坏婚礼?
That's what this is aII about, isn't it? You want to fuck up the wedding.
这一点都不好笑 卡玛 一点都不好笑!
It's not fucking funny, Kumar. It's not fucking funny!
在这节骨眼上 只有柯尔特能帮我们了
CoIton is the onIy guy that can heIp us out at this point.
真不敢相信 你居然打算去搞破坏
I can't beIieveI cannot beIieve you're wiIIing to fuck that up!
我只是看他不爽而已
I just hate that fucking asshoIe, OK?
是么? 现在我看他可比看你顺眼多了
Yeah? I Iike him better than I Iike you right now.
真的?      是的
ReaIIy?         Yeah.
你知道他给了我什么吗? 一份工作
You know what he got me? A job.
而你呢? 把我送进了关塔那摩监狱
You know what you got me? Thrown into Guantanamo Bay.
你的工作烂透了      承认吧
Your job sucks.         Admit it.
你嫉妒是因为温妮莎找了个比你更优秀的人
You're jeaIous because Vanessa found somebody better than you.
你他妈的什么意思?
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
就是比你强! 我想想
Better than you! Let me think.
未来的总统 还是吊儿郎当的瘾君子?
PotentiaI future president, or unempIoyed pothead?
难啊 太难了
Tough. That's tough.
对她来说真是个艰难的选择啊! 对吧?
That's a tough one for her, isn't it?
对啊 至少温妮莎不在阿姆斯特丹
Yeah, weII at Ieast Vanessa's not in Amsterdam...
被一群欧洲佬操
getting pIowed by a bunch of European dudes.
什么?      你真的以为玛利亚会为你
What?         Do you reaIIy think Maria's...
守身如玉吗?
saving herseIf for you, dude?
现在可能有两条异国鸡巴
Right now, she's probabIy got two uncircumcised dicks...
在她面前晃荡
dangIing in front of her throat.
你知道她会怎么做吗?深深的插到嘴巴里
You know what she's gonna do with them? Down 'em into her tonsiIs?
操你老母!
Fucking dick.
那是我的帽子      那是我的帽子 哥们
That's my hat.         That was my hat, bro.
玛利亚 玛利亚 玛利亚 玛利亚
Maria, Maria, Maria, Maria.
混蛋!
AsshoIe!
让你再对我的天使多说一个字!
Don't you dare say a fucking word about my angeI!
那是什么?
What the fuck was that?
起来 起来!
Get up. Get up!
妈的
Fuck you.
操
Shit.
那不是三K党的篝火吗?
Isn't that a KKK bonfire?
是的
Yeah.
我想是的
Yeah, I think it is.
我们最好马上闪
Maybe we shouId get the fuck out of here.
是的 哥们
Yeah. Yeah, dude.
快闪
Let's do that.
那天我重看了贝克汉姆的比赛
The other day, caught a rerun of that show Becker.
你知道那场比赛吗?
You know that show?
是的 和犹太人泰德丹深的那场
Yeah, that's the one with that Jew, Ted Danson.
那个金发黑人一到那儿 我们都笑翻了
That bIond negro they got on there, he had me in stitches.
他真的很搞笑
He's actuaIIy pretty funny.
是吗? 你这么认为?
ReaIIy? You think so?
我不是说我不会虐待那个男的 但是...
I'm not saying I wouIdn't Iynch the guy, but...
他的时机是无价的
his timing, it's priceIess.
等一下
HoId up a second.
我去释放一下
I gotta go drain the main vein.
我跟你说 塔唯斯
I'II teII ya, Travis...
当我感觉很爽的时候
when it comes to feeIing good...
我会边高潮边尿尿拉屎
I'd rate pissin' right up there with comin' and shittin'.
我喜欢三个一起来
I Iike to do aII three.
对 我知道了
Yeah, I hear ya.
肯尼 你他妈快点
Kenny, come on, man. Hurry the fuck up.
是你让我喝第三瓶啤酒的
You were the one who made me drink that third beer.
耐心点
HoId your horses, peckerwood.
恶! 你丫尿到我身上了!
Gross! You fucking pissed on me!
你这只种族歧视猪      怎么回事?
You racist fuck!         What the heck?
那个黑鬼是谁?
What the nigger was that?
什么衰事 我们衰死了
This is fucked. We are fucked.
肯尼 塔唯斯
Kenny. Travis.
你们俩在鬼叫什么
What in the tarnation you guys doin'?
很好 你们把小桶拿来了 把它拖过来
Good, you brought the keg. Lug that thing over.
走啊 来啊      来吧
Let's go! Come on!         Come on!
来吧!
Let's go, come on!
然后你在上面放点洋葱蒸起来 棒极了
Yeah, then you put IittIe onions on 'em and you steam 'em, they're awesome.
罗迪 伙计 我从没想过我会说这个
RoIdy, dude, I'd never thought I'd say this in a miIIion years...
但是 三K党很懂得搞派对
but the KIan reaIIy knows how to party.
你得试试看这些
You gotta try these dogs.
真的?      是的
ReaIIy?         Oh, yeah.
真的…三K党很会搞派对?
ReaIIy know how to the KIan knows how to party?
哥们我们得闪     天啊 好的 放松点
Dude, we've got to get out of here!         Jeez, aII right, dude, reIax.
好了 大伙儿 都过来 围着篝火坐一圈
AII right, y'aII! Come on over here and we'II sit around the campfire.
操 怎么办      去坐吧
Shit, what do we do?         Let's go sit down.
卢弗斯 坐在蜜饯和全麦饼干旁边
Rufus. Next to them marshmaIIows and the graham crackers.
我们很久没有聚会了
Best s'mores we've had in a Iong time...
这就是我想说的
that's what I'm taIking about, that's what I'm taIking about.
现在我要你们一个个告诉我
Now. Now I want each one of y'aII to teII me...
一些关于犹太猪的事
somethin'Porch monkey, kike!
你们这星期对少数民族做的事
...that you did to a minority this week. Yeah.
有一天我在沃尔玛走下楼梯时
I tripped a beaner whiIe I was waIking down the stairs...
骂了一个墨西哥傻逼
at the WaIMart the other day.
他撞进了一堆酒瓶子里
Guy crashed into a bunch of wine bottIes.
他赔了所有的钱!
They made him pay for 'em! Yeah!
好的好的 我们冷静一下
AII right, aII right, Iet's aII caIm down.
白人万岁 白人万岁 白人万岁
White power here, white power here, white power here.
他活该!
Giving him what he deserves.
噫!
Hebe!
好了 我回神了 下一个
AII right, I'm back. Next.
最好更火爆点 你
It better be good. Here.
说吧 说点什么
Come on, dude, say something.
你知道吗?
You know what?
我顶了一个印第安佬的蛋蛋
I did knee an Indian guy in the baIIs.
真有意思
That's funny!
是的 然后把那些印第安佬送回非洲去了
Yeah, send them Indians back to Africa.
你想不想听听我干的一些很有搞头的事?
WeII, you want to hear something reaI fuckedup and awesome that I did?
我拿了一个韩国家伙的牙刷来刷我的小弟弟
I took a Korean guy's toothbrush and I rubbed it aII over my dick.
你真的做过?      那真是恶心啊
You did that?         WeII, that's just downright disgustin'.
但是我喜欢      耶!
But I Iike it!         Yeah!
耶 我喜欢当白人
Yeah, I Iove bein' white.
怎么      看看我们捉到什么了 兄弟们
What the         Look what we got us here, brothers.
墨西哥人!
Mexicans!
虐死他们!
Lynch 'em!
快 快 快!
Come on, come on! Come on!
快啊 让我们把他们驱逐到边境去
Come on, boys, Iet's chase them back to the border!
你奶奶的胸!
Pussy fart!
操!
HoIy shit!
我们要灭火吗还是怎么样?
ShouId we put it out or what?
他们还在追我们吗?
Are they stiII behind us?
我看没有 兄弟 三K党真他妈慢
I don't think so. Dude, the KIan is fucking sIow.
诶 让那车停下来
Hey, fIag down this car.
救命! 救命! 救命!
HeIp! HeIp! HeIp!
谢谢      谢谢
Thank you.         Thank you.
~ 耶 ~
~ Yeah ~
谢谢你停下来
Thanks for stopping.
~ 最好检查你自己 ~
~ You better check yo seIf ~
没事
No probIem.
~ 因为我对你的健康不利 我偷偷的来 ~
~'Cause I'm bad for your heaIth, I come reaI steaIth ~
尼奥?
NeiI?
盖瑞和卡玛!
Gary and Kumar!
是的       是的
Yeah.         Yeah.
哈罗德 哈罗德
HaroId. HaroId.
不好意思 我忘了
Sorry, man. I forgot.
你在这干嘛 兄弟?
What are you doing here, man?
是上帝指引我来的 你们在这干嘛?
This is where God took me. What are you guys doing out here?
实际上我们想去德克萨斯
We're actuaIIy trying to get to Texas.
我正要去那!
That's where I'm headed!
真巧啊
What are the odds?
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
好的      谢谢
AII right.         Thank you.
迷幻剂?
Shrooms?
谢谢 不要      谢谢不要
No. Thanks, though.         No, thank you.
请随意
Suit yourseIf.
先生们 开动你们的马达吧
GentIemen, start your engines.
这将是颠簸崎岖的旅程
It's gonna be a bumpy fuckin' ride.
~ 因为子弹有害健康 ~
~'Cause shotgun buIIets are bad for your heaIth ~
我们找到他们的手机了
We found their phone.
李和派特给你们打过电话
Lee and PateI made a phone caII to you.
现在把你们知道的他们恐怖行动说出来
Now teII us everything you know about their terrorist pIot.
恐怖行动? 罗迪和卡玛?
Terrorist pIot? RoId and Kumar?
荒唐
This is ridicuIous.
好吧 好的 好的
OK, fine. Fine.
罗森布格先生
Mr. Rosenberg.
格德斯坦先生
Mr. GoIdstein.
就按你们的方法来吧
We'II do it your way.
这是什么? 我手里拿着什么?
What's this? What do we have here?
这里有7美元?
It's about seven doIIars?
别侮辱我们 好吗?
Look, don't insuIt us, aII right?
我不知道这到底在搞什么名堂?
I don't know what the heII is going on here...
但是我请求沉默的权利 直到我的律师来
but I'm pIeading the Fifth untiI I speak to my Iawyer.
你要求沉默 哈?
You're pIeading the Fifth, huh?
比彻 给我一本人权法案
Beecher, give me a copy of the BiII of Rights.
人权法案? 为什么
The BiII of Rights? Why?
去干就是了!
Just do it!
对不起
Excuse me.
第五条 是吧?
Five, right?
第五条万岁      当然
Five aIive.         Sure.
好吧 好吧 好的
OK. OK. Good.
你想知道我怎么认为第五条修正案的吗?
You wanna know what I think about the Fifth Amendment?
就是这样
There it is.
我认为第五条修正案就是这样
That's what I think of the Fifth Amendment.
为什么你屁股这么脏?你不擦吗?
Why the heII is your ass so dirty? Don't you wipe?
别问问题 你不会想知道答案的
Don't ask questions you don't want the answer to, buddy.
问出什么了
What do ya got?
FBI已经在窃听格德斯坦先生的电话了
Turns out the FBI was aIready tapping Mr. GoIdstein's phone.
我们要的到手了      等一下
We got what we need.         Wait a second.
你窃听我的电话?
You were tapping my phone?
你要听磁带吗?
You want to hear the tape?
听这个脏农夫的话真恶心 结果如何?
No. I'm sick of Iistening to this dirt farmer. What's the upshot?
李和派特在去德克萨斯路上 正如我们所料
Lee and PateI are on their way to Texas as we speak.
我就知道他们动身了
I knew they'd trip up.
准备飞机 这些兔崽子死定了
Ready the pIane. These fuckers are goin' down.
尼奥 你能专心开车吗?你应该看路
NeiI, can you just focus on driving? You've hadFocus on the road.
你吃了够多了 朋友
You've had dozens of shrooms, my friend.
哥们 我14岁就动了阑尾炎手术
Dude, I was abIe to perform an appendectomy at age 14.
不就几个迷幻剂嘛 我对付得了
I think I can handIe a coupIe mushrooms.
那不是个电视节目吗?      噢 我的天哪
Wasn't that just a TV show?         Jesus Christ!
你们看到那个独角兽了吗?
Did you see that unicorn?
它的角真亮!
Its horn was so shiny.
那你们俩去德克萨斯干嘛?
So, why are you guys headed to Texas?
我的前女友要结婚了
Let's just say my exgirIfriend's getting married.
离开你的那个?
The one that got away, huh?
是的
Yep.
在我看来，你需要喝一杯
Sounds to me Iike you need a drink.
请看路 尼奥 你能注意一下...
Road. NeiI, pIease, can you pay attention
兄弟 我知道了
Dude, I've got it!
是的 但是…      他是个好司机 别说了
Yeah, but         He's a good driver. Stop.
谢谢 干杯 兄弟
Thanks, man. Cheers, dude.
真的? 喝酒?
ReaIIy? Drinking?
我也有一个失去真爱的故事
I have a IostIove story of my own.
是吗?
Yeah?
在《紫色爱心》开机的时候发生的事
Happened on the set of CIara's Heart.
当然当然
Sure, sure, yeah.
我永远忘不了她 她的名字是塔松达
I'II never forget her. Her name was Tashonda.
她是伍匹格德布格的替身
She was Whoopi GoIdberg's standin.
她的皮肤柔软 嘴唇真甜
Her skin was so soft, her Iips were so sweet.
她的奶头就像好时巧克力一样...
She had these tiny, IittIe Hershey Kiss nippIes...
你会整晚上都想吸着她
that you just wanted to suck on aII night Iong.
不管怎么样 拍电影的最后一天 我跟她说
Anyway, Iast day of shooting, I toId her.
我说...
I said...
"我们应该分手了"
''TBird, we're gonna have to break up.''
你为什么那样做
Why did you do that?
我认为我无法承担那样的责任
I didn't think I couId take on that kind of responsibiIity.
真是个大错误
It was such a big mistake.
为什么? 我是说 她走了以后
Why? I mean, with TBird gone...
你就不能和别的人上床了吗?
couIdn't you have sex with whoever you wanted?
让我说清楚点
Let me be cIear.
这个星球上没有什么
There is nothing on the pIanet...
比一个热情的新的女人更让我着迷了
that I Iove more than a hot, new pussy.
当然      没有
Sure.         Nothing.
P.H.是什么意思?
What does the P.H. stands for in N.P.H.?
帕迪克哈里斯
Patrick Harris.
错 大众错误 是把妹高手
No, common mistake. Poon handIer.
男孩们 关键是...
The point is, boys...
虽然我喜欢和一些辣妹上床
even though I Iove havin' sex with some hot, random trim...
但是没有哪一天我不在想念塔松达的
a day hasn't gone by where I haven't thought of Tashonda.
每次我一看到好时巧克力 我的蛋蛋就湿了
Every time I see a bag of Hershey's Kisses, my baIIs get so wet.
为了塔松达干杯
Here's to you, Tashonda.
希望你没把孩子打掉      哇
I hope you kept the baby.         Wow.
~ 我一个人自由自在 ~
~ Free on my own ~
~ 我向来如此 ~
~ That's the way I used to be ~
~ 但自从遇见你 宝贝 ~
~ But since I met you, baby ~
嘿 亲爱的 怎么了?
Hey, honey. What's up?
我在你口袋里找到个东西
I found something in your purse.
你干嘛翻我的袋子?
Why wouId you go through my purse?
你怎么会有大麻
Why wouId you have a joint...
你知道这会毁了我的政治生涯
when you know it couId ruin my poIiticaI career?
对不起
I'm sorry.
因为结婚的那些事我有点压力
What with aII the wedding pIans, I've just been a IittIe stressed.
它能让我放松放松
It heIps me reIax?
大麻是违法的 温妮莎
Marijuana is iIIegaI, Vanessa.
我以为你生活中的那段时间已经是过去式了
Now, I thought that part of your Iife was in the past.
是的      好的
It is.         Good.
我就想听到这个
That's aII I need to hear.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby.
我知道因为结婚会紧张兴奋
Look, I know things can be hectic with the wedding.
但是你知道如果你压力太大 就像我一样
But, you know, if you get stressed out, just do what I do.
吃抗抑郁药 好吗?
Snort ZoIoft, OK?
搞毛啊
What the fuck?
操
Shit.
兄弟们 他们搞了个鬼路障 我们会被发现的
Dude, they set up a fucking roadbIock! They're gonna find us.
你们在说什么?      尼奥....
What are you taIking about?         NeiI...
我不知道怎么说好 但我们是在逃通缉犯
I don't know how to say this any other way, man, but we're fugitives.
酷
CooI.
好的 我们得整个法子逃走
OK, weII, we've got to find a way to get out of this.
是的 是的 是的       拜托
Yeah, yeah, yeah.         PIease.
你们别搞得好像我从没偷渡过通缉犯一样
You act Iike I've never smuggIed a fugitive across state Iines before.
给 藏这
Here. Hide in that.
不好意思 有点粘
Sorry. It's a IittIe sticky.
操
Shit.
爽
Yeah.
搞什么…你打算什么时候给我看这些?
What theWhen were you gonna show me these?
对不起
Excuse me.
等一下 长官
Wait, Officer!
操      让那车停下
Shit.         HoId that car!
尼奥・帕迪克・哈里斯
NeiI Patrick Harris.
好啊
Yo.
很荣幸遇到你 先生
It is an honor to meet you, sir.
是的 我能想像
Yeah. I wouId imagine so.
我想你总是会碰到这样的情况
I'm sure you get this aII the time...
但你在星河战队的演出真的改变了我的生活
but your part in StarshIp Troopers truIy, truIy changed my Iife.
真的?
ReaIIy?
怎么改变了?
How?
没人想到对虫族的战争会赢
WeII, no one thought the war against the arachnids of KIendathu couId be won.
但是你展示了星河战队…      尼奥
But you showed the starship troopers         NeiI!
可以摧毁那些臭虫们
...that those bugs couId be destroyed.
很多人认为那个反恐战争是不能赢的 是吧?
A Iot of peopIe think the war on terror is a war that can't be won, right?
这就是我加入国家安全局的原因
That's why I joined the Department of HomeIand Security.
我的朋友 两个字 牛逼队
My friend, two words. StarshIp fuckin' Troopers.
如果你想知道人类的秘密 跟我来
If you want to know the secret of being, you wiII come with us.
对不起 我真的要走了
PIease. I reaIIy need to go.
当然 很抱歉打扰了这么久 您自便
Yeah, of course. I'm so sorry to bother you. You move aIong.
再见
Bye.
我爱你
I Iove you.
我也爱你 帕迪克哈里斯先生
I Iove you too, Mr. Patrick Harris.
搞什...
What the
操你个逼 刚才真牛
HoIy fucking shit, that was awesome.
你们试试看吃了迷幻药还有那样的对话
Try having that conversation on shrooms.
奥斯卡应该给我刚才的表现颁奖
I deserve an Oscar for that performance.
应该的      兄弟们
You do!         Dudes...
我要绕个道 可以吗?
I'm gonna take a IittIe detour on the way, aII right?
不行      尼奥 别啊
No.         NeiI, no.
但是我们都快到了
But we're aImost there, man.
没有但是      你想干...
No buts. No buts!         What do you do
我要去鸡店去爽爽
I'm going to a whorehouse and I'm gonna get my fuck on.
你们不想动鸡巴的话 没事啊
If you two don't want to get your dicks wet, that's fine with me.
我要去活动活动我的小弟弟
I'II get my dick wet.
~ 什么都不需要 只要一段好时光 ~
~ Don't need nothin' but a good time ~
~ 我如何抗拒? ~
~ How can I resist? ~
~ 什么都不要 就要一段好时光 ~
~ Ain't Iookin' for nothin' but a good time ~
~ 没有什么会比这好 ~
~ And it don't get better than this ~
小贱人 我来了!
Pussy, I'm home!
人呢?
HeIIo?
哎哟哟 我以为你再也不敢来了呢
WeII, weII, weII. I thought you'd never show your face around here again.
怎么了莎莉
What's the matter, SaIIy?
我以为我是你们这金牌客户之一
I thought I was one of your top customers.
你忘了上次你来干了些什么吗?
Have you forgotten what happened the Iast time you were here?
因为你 我的头牌走了
Because of you, my best girI quit.
嘿 我给她很多钱
Hey, I paid her good money.
关我鸟事 她湿不了
It's not my fauIt she didn't Iube up.
还有 我给你介绍新客户来了
Besides, I bring you new customers.
新客户      别啊 尼奥 够了
New customers?         No, NeiI, that's aII.
谢谢谢谢 很感谢
Thank you. Thank you. Appreciate it. Appreciate it.
莎莉 把队伍拉出来
SaIIy. Bring on the Iineup.
排好队 姑娘们
Line up in the chutes, girIs.
长号吹响了
Longhorns coming through.
尼奥
NeiI.
大波 大波 大波 大波
Bigger. Bigger. Bigger. Bigger.
你好 --
HeIIo, ba
你叫什么 小姐      奶头海明威
What's your name, miss?         Tits Hemingway.
你的名字怎么来的
How'd you come up with that?
我有巨乳
WeII, I have huge tits.
我最喜欢的书是《移动的盛宴》
And my favorite book is A MoveabIe Feast.
我觉得有点道理
I guess that makes sense, yeah.
希望你准备好要我了 奶头
WeII, I hope you're ready for me, Tits...
因为我的老二枪已上膛
'cause I'm gonna rock out with my cock out...
你等着被我射死吧
and you're gonna jam out with your cIam out.
神奇的好戏就要来了
It's gonna be magicaI.
这妞我要了 兄弟      不 尼奥
The whores are on me, feIIas.         No, NeiI...
谢谢 但是我们 那个...      谢谢 哥们
thank you, but wethat's         Thanks, dude.
忘了那些 罗迪 我不知道你...
Screw that, RoIdy. I don't know about you...
但是不是对其他人不敬 我要这两个
but, no offense to the rest of you Iadies, I am gonna be taking you two.
别啊 卡玛 卡玛!
No, Kumar. Kumar!
罗迪 你搞错状况了 哥们
RoIdy, you're missing out, brother.
嘿 我们需要马上上路
Yo, we need to get back on the road, buddy.
我们得
We need
那个 现在 你知道我们还提供
WeII, now, you know, we aIso suppIy...
室内电影和杂志
inroom fiIms or a magazine.
如果你想自己来
WeII, if you'd Iike some seIfsatisfaction...
我们还有一些
we do have some...
电子设备就在那里
eIectronic devices right over there.
就来杯咖啡吧 好吗?
Just have some coffee. Yeah?
你为什么不躺下去呢?
Why don't you Iie on the bed?
告诉我们你想我们怎么做
And teII us what you want us to do.
好的 好的
OK. OK.
那...
WeII...
不如...
how about
不如你们脱了衣服 你们互搞?
How about you take off your cIothes and make out with each other?
我们以前这么做过      可以的
We've done that before.         We can do that.
可以      是的
Yeah?         Yeah.
~ 洞洞真好 ~
~ Pussy reaI good ~
~ 那个洞 洞洞真好 ~
~ That pussy Pussy reaI good ~
~ 那个洞 拉链后面的洞洞 ~
~ That pussy That pussy off the chain ~
~ 那个洞 来吧随你搞 ~
~ That pussy Go on and do yo thang ~
~ 那个洞 洞洞真好 ~
~ That pussy Pussy reaI good ~
~ That pussy That pussy reaI good ~
~ 那个洞 ~
~ That pussy ~
~ 你妈妈不喜欢 ~
~ Yo' mama don't Iike ~
~ 她说我不好 ~
~ She say I'm no good ~
~ 她不知道的是 ~
~ What she don't know is ~
~ 我让你叫得欢 ~
~ I got you pussywhooped ~
~ 他需要这个洞洞 ~
~ He need this pussy ~
~ 他闻着这里 ~
~ He smeII this pussy ~
~ 他要尝这里 ~
~ He wanna taste this pussy ~
~ 他要付钱给这里 ~
~ He gotta pay for pussy ~
能舌吻吗?
Can you use tongue?
~ 那个洞 洞 ~
~ That pussy, pussy ~
~ 洞 洞 ~
~ Pussy, pussy ~
把你的奶子压到她奶子上去
Bump your titty on her titty.
~ 警察把我按倒 ~
~ PoIice puII me over ~
~ 他们没有开罚单 ~
~ They don't write no tickets ~
勃起了
Boner achieved!
太好了 现在先脱裤子
Great. Now Iet's get those pants off.
好的
OK.
你们真是善良的人      是的 我们知道
You are benevoIent human beings.         Yeah, I know.
是吗      很多人这么说
Yeah?         We get that a Iot.
你知道我说的"善良"是什么意思?
Yeah. You know what that means, benevoIent?
是的 我知道
Yeah, I do, actuaIIy.
什么意思?
What?
它的意思是我们会把你操倒
It means we're gonna fuck you so hard...
你的小弟弟要酸痛两个星期
your dick's gonna be sore for two weeks.
我就是这个意思
That is exactIy, exactIy what it means.
你知道 我最头痛什么吗?
You know what bothers me the most, though?
他从来没为把我卷进这件事道过歉
He never once apoIogized for getting me into aII this troubIe.
我现在本该和我的玛利亚在阿姆斯特丹
I mean, I'm supposed to be with my Maria right now in Amsterdam, OK?
算了 他不知道怎么说"对不起"
But it's cooI. He doesn't know how to say ''I'm sorry.''
为什么他不会说?
Why do you think that is?
因为他只知道他想要的 他他还是他
SparkIe, because it's aII about what he wants. It's about him, him, him.
其实 我不在意 因为 你知道...
You know. I don't even care becauseYou know
如果他不把我当好朋友 我也不会
if he can't be a good friend to me, I'm not gonna be a good friend to him.
就这样      别这么说
It's done.         Don't say that.
一个好朋友是很难得的
A good friend is hard to come by.
维纳斯 拜托
Venus, come on.
但如果他真的是个好朋友 他会知道道歉
Yeah, but if he was a reaI friend, he wouId know how to say, ''I'm sorry.''
对啊
That's right.
谢谢 阿柯斯
Thank you, Agnes.
一语中的
NaiI on the head.
就像现在
It's Iike right now...
在经历这些天的衰事后
after aII the shit that we have been through in the Iast few days...
你知道 他现在在这里享乐 搞女人
you know, he's in there having the time of his Iife, having sex.
我不应该离开她的
I never shouId have Ieft her.
我甚至不知道
I don't even know
我甚至不知道那时候我想些什么
I don't even know what I was thinking.
我那么爱她
I Ioved her so much.
她是我的小宝贝
She was my IittIe baby.
我怎么会让我的宝贝离开我呢?
Why did I Iet my IittIe baby go?
我怎能让她走呢?
Why did I Iet her go?
你会找到其他人的
You'II find someone eIse.
不会的 没人像温妮莎那样的
No, I won't. Not Iike Vanessa.
总有一天你会找到爱的
You'II find Iove again someday.
会的
Yeah, you wiII.
你们找到过真爱吗?
Did you guys?
没有 我们是妓女
No, we're whores.
难道你忘了?     哦是的
Remember?         Yeah.
天啊 你还好吧
Oh, my God. Are you OK?
这里在搞什么飞机?
What the heII is going on here?
那个变态给我打了烙印
That prick fucking branded me!
好了      我警告过你了 尼奥
Stop it.         I warned you, NeiI.
你来啊
Bring it.
尼奥! 尼奥!      是时候让你老二去死了
NeiI! NeiI!         Time to put your dick in the dirt.
什么? 尼奥 你干了什么?      快走快走
WhatNeiI! What are you doing?         Come on. Come on. Come on.
但是      别 尼奥
But         No, NeiI.
尼奥
NeiI!
尼奥怎么办      操他妈尼奥 他害了我们
What about NeiI, man?         No, fuck NeiI. He just fucked us.
尼奥尼奥     快上来啊快快
NeiI! NeiI!         Come on, come on, come on!
快快快      尼奥
Come on! Come on! Come on!         NeiI!
快点
Come on!
尼奥帕迪克哈里斯     不
N.P.H.!         No!
停 停
Stop! Stop!
等等 等等 我们得带上尼奥
Wait, wait, wait, wait! We've got to get NeiI.
为什么     我们在偷他的车
Why?         Look, we're steaIing his car!
我们不能把他留在那里
We can't Ieave him back there.
他上星期偷了你的车
He stoIe your fucking car Iast week!
那是什么
What was that?
快点      尼奥
Hurry up.         NeiI!
快点 快来      兄弟们
Hurry up. Come on, man.         Guys.
好了 快来 快来 快上来      尼奥 快啊
AII right. Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.         NeiI, NeiI, come on! Come on, man!
兄弟们      快啊 快啊
Guys!         Hurry up! Hurry up!
这一点都不有趣 快点
It's not even funny. Hurry up, dude, hurry up.
你能行的
You can make it, dude.
天啊 天啊
Oh, my God! HoIy shit!
上帝啊 上帝啊      我的上帝啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!         Jesus Christ!
尼奥死了 尼奥死了      不!
NeiI's dead! NeiI's dead!         No!
天啊      快逃出这鬼地方 走啊走
Oh, my God!         Get the fuck out of here! Go! Go!
~ 我怎么说再见 ~
~ How do I say goodbye ~
他妈的又是一天
It's the dawn of a new day.
可是尼奥帕迪克哈里斯看不到了
And NeiI Patrick Harris isn't around to see it, man.
哥们 我跟你说过
Dude, I toId you.
你别说了行不?
WiII you pIease stop saying that?
上帝啊
God.
他死了
He's gone.
可能这里会有他的家庭联系信息
Maybe he's got some famiIy contact info in here.
哥们 我知道我不会打电话给他父母的
Dude, I know I'm not caIIing NeiI's parents.
包里啥?
What's in the bag?
奶奶的胸      诡异的面具
HoIy fuck.         Creepy mask.
装着头发的罐子
A jar with hair in it.
好像是 12瓶防狼剂
And, Iike, 1 2 cans of Mace.
看啊 伙计      他奶奶的胸
Look, dude.         HoIy shit.
操 我们真的到了
HoIy shit, we actuaIIy made it.
这里就是柯尔特长大的地方吧
This is where CoIton grew up, huh?
闻到没? 闻起来像喷水器
SmeII that? That smeIIs Iike douche.
不 你呆在车里
No, you wiII remain in this car.
我单独进去 如果我们走运
I wiII go inside aIone and, if we're Iucky
柯尔特会把我们救出去
CoIton wiII heIp us out.
为什么我不能      不 换句话说
Why can't I just         No. Let me put it another way.
你下车 我们的友谊就玩完
You Ieave this car, and our friendship is over.
但是 罗德 我只想      卡玛
But, RoIdy, I just         Kumar.
开门 不然我就把你的蛋蛋切掉
Open the door and I wiII cut your fucking baIIs off.
天啊 好吧
Jesus. OK.
蛋蛋      去吧
BaIIs.         Go.
你好 我是柯尔特的朋友
Hi, I'm a friend of CoIton's.
谢谢
Thank you.
靠
God damn it.
温妮莎 你还好吗?
Vanessa? You OK?
卡玛 你在这干嘛?      我扶你
Kumar? What are you doing here?         Yeah, Iet me heIp you up.
我以为你去阿姆斯特丹了
I thought you were going to Amsterdam.
是啊 我也以为 但不行了
Yeah, me too. It didn't work out.
你还好吧
You aII right?
我碰到的时候 痛吗?     痛
Now, does this hurt when I touch it?         Yeah.
痛?      是的
It does?         Yeah.
这就是我要的 婚礼上一瘸一拐的
This is just what I need. A Iimp during the wedding.
你能把它转一下吗?
Can you move it around in a circIe?
好的 我知道了 你脚踝扭伤了 但是没裂开
OK, that's what I figured. It's just your ATFL. I don't think you tore it, though.
来点冰和按摩会好的 会好的
So a IittIe ice and massage shouId do the trick. You'II be fine.
你想告诉我 你为什么在这里吗?
Are you gonna teII me why you're here?
我和罗迪有了点麻烦
RoIdy and I ran into some troubIe...
我们想可能你的柯尔特能帮帮我们
and we figured that maybe your CoIton couId heIp us out.
又碰到麻烦了 哈?      有一点
StiII getting into troubIe, huh?         A IittIe bit.
你还记得有一次你闯入动物实验室
You remember that time that you broke into the animaI Iab...
你偷走了那只猴
and, Iike, stoIe that monkey
然后把它放进了罗森伯格的宿舍里
and put it in Andy Rosenberg's dorm room?
好的 首先这是格德斯坦的主意
OK, first of aII, that was GoIdstein's idea...
其次
and second of aII...
如果我知道那猴子有爱滋病
had I known that the monkey had AIDS
我永远都不会那么做的
I never wouId have done that.
你呢?
What about you?
你把那些恶心的用过的卫生巾
You put those disgusting used tampons
放到教授的手袋里
in Professor Konop's purse.
还记得吗?      少来了
Remember that?         Come on.
她是个婊子 你知道的
She was a bitch and you know it.
发生什么事了
What's going on here?
嘿 她摔倒了 后跟摔到了
Hey, she actuaIIy feII and broke her heeI here.
是的 我踝骨扭伤了 卡玛正在帮我看
Yeah, I twisted my ankIe. Kumar was just Iooking at it.
你为什么不在车上 卡玛?
Why aren't you in the car, Kumar?
哥们我听到她大叫一声
Dude, I heard her yeII.
我想我跟你说过呆在车里
I thought I toId you to stay in the car, man.
没事 兄弟
It's OK, man.
别担心
No worries.
听着 罗迪跟我说什么情况
Listen, RoIdy fiIIed me in on the situation.
但是别担心 我会让我爸把事情都搞定的
But don't worry. I'II make sure my dad takes care of everything.
谢了 兄弟
Thanks, man.
现在你得去看看医生
In the meantime, you are going to the doctor.
拉蒙!
Ramon!
拉蒙 把温妮莎马上带到哈里斯医生那
Ramon. PIease bring Vanessa to Dr. Harris immediateIy.
再见 希望你能好起来
Bye, Vanessa. Hope you feeI better.
再见      再见
Bye.         Bye.
伙计们
Guys.
好了
AII right.
好了伙计们 飞机油都加好了
AII right, guys. Jet's aII fueIed.
一会你们就到家了
You shouId be home in no time.
太贴心了
Sweet.
嘿 柯尔特我真不敢相信在你婚礼的前一天
Hey, CoIton, I can't beIieve you're doing this for us...
为我们做了这些
on the night before your wedding day.
真的很感谢 谢谢      小事一桩
I reaIIy appreciate it. Thank you.         PIease don't mention it.
只是想确认所有的事都没问题
Just want to make sure everything works out smoothIy.
这些飞机都是你的吗?
Are aII these pIanes yours?
不是的 好吧
No. OK.
罗迪 拜托 当然是啦
RoId, come on, of course they are.
这个人真搞笑 你很搞笑
This guy's funny. You're funny.
是吗?      嘿 柯尔特
Yeah?         Hey, CoIton, man.
听着 我想我错怪你了 你不是个傻逼
Listen, I was wrong about you, dude. You're not a douchebag.
诶!
Dude.
你知道我说的 我是说 你丫不错
You know what I mean. I mean, you're a good dude.
我为你和温妮莎高兴
And I'm happy for you and Vanessa.
你真伟大 卡玛
That's big of you, Kumar.
我真的很感谢      当然
I reaIIy appreciate it.         Sure.
我等不及要回去了
I just can't wait to get back, man.
你们会回去的
You're going back aII right.
这次你逃不走了
This time you're not escaping.
现在
Now!
行动!
Go! Move, move, move!
你整一个傻逼
You are a douchebag
不会吧      操你个傻逼 操死你
No.         ...you fucking douchebag, fuck you!
是的 我最不想看到你们俩来破坏我的婚礼
Yeah. The Iast thing I was Ietting you guys do is ruin my wedding.
你搞的鬼?      当然是他
You did this?         Of course he did this.
我以为我们是朋友 你怎么能这样背叛我们
I thought we were friends, man. How couId you betray me Iike this?
拜托 罗迪 你和我吗?
Come on, RoId. You and me?
你帮我在高等数学中作弊
You Iet me cheat off you in Advanced Accounting.
要不是这样 我鸟都不会鸟你
Other than that, I couId give a shit about you.
带走!
Take 'em away, guys.
一旦我们出来我要把你的屁股操烂
When we get out of this I'm gonna fucking kick your fucking ass, man!
你吓死我了
Boy, you're scaring me.
来啊 你又不是会功夫的亚洲人
WeII, come on, you're not one of those kungfu Asians...
看在上帝的份上 你就是一个婊子操的
you're a fucking pussy banker, for Christ's sakes.
操你妈 操你妈      我要把撕成八块 贱人
Fuck you! Fuck you!         I'm gonna rip you up, bitch!
还是先顾好你自己吧 贱人      操你老母!
You'd best watch your back, bitch!         Fuck you, dude!
操你      操死你
Fuck you!         Fuck you!
我太彪悍了
I'm awesome.
看来你们挑错人了 哈?
Looks Iike you boys picked the wrong side, huh?
你们的真神阿拉呢?
Where's your Koran now?
我们又不是穆斯林 你个低能...
We're not even MusIim, you moron...
即使我们是穆斯林也不代表我们恐怖分子啊
and even if we were, that doesn't make us terrorists.
嘿 我在和你说话 过来!
Hey! I'm taIking to you. Get back here!
~ 紧张下的情绪 你开始抚摸我 ~
~ MetaI under tension beggin' you to touch and go ~
~ 很High ~
~ Highway to ~
哥们我真无法置信我们要被送回去了
Man. I can't beIieve we're going back.
现在你知道我为什么讨厌柯尔特了吗?
Now do you see why I hate CoIton Graham?
你现在知道我为什么讨厌你了吗?
Now do you see why I hate you?
我特意吩咐你呆在车里
I asked you specificaIIy to stay in the car.
我跟你说我们的友谊千钧一发了
I toId you our friendship was at stake.
温妮莎摔倒了 我得去帮她
Vanessa feII down. And I was heIping her.
我不想听借口      那不是借口
I don't want to hear the excuses!         It's not an excuse!
我不想听任何借口!
I don't want to hear the excuses!
我听到她叫了      我不想听
I heard her yeIIing!         I don't want to hear it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
好吗?
'Kay?
看看
Look at this. Look at this.
我把事情搞砸了
I fucked up, OK?
我总是把事情搞砸 我就是个烂人
I fucked up and I aIways fuck up. I am a fuckup.
你觉得?
You think?
哈罗德
HaroId...
你是我最好的朋友 兄弟
you're my best friend, dude.
你是我的一切 我爱你
You mean the worId to me, man. I Iove you.
断臂男
Queers.
我答应你 一旦我们
And I promise you, if we figure out...
能逃出去我就改变 好吗?
a way to get out of this, I'm gonna change, OK?
事情不会总围着我转的
It's not just gonna be about Kumar aII the time.
而是卡玛和哈罗德两人的事情
It'II be about Kumar and HaroId.
哈罗德和卡玛
HaroId and Kumar.
我喜欢卡玛放在前面
I kind of Iike the first way better.
好的好的 哈罗德和卡玛
OK, OK. HaroId and Kumar.
哈罗德和卡玛
HaroId and Kumar.
~ 紧张感越强 ~
~ The hotter the intensity ~
这不全怪你
It's not aII your fauIt.
是的 我只是把大麻带上飞机了
Yeah, it is. I brought weed on the pIane.
你有大麻?     没有 是另一架飞机
You got weed?         No. The other pIane.
我希望尼奥还活着 那狗屁军官爱死他了
No, I wish NeiI Patrick Harris were stiII aIive, that guy fucking Ioves him.
他能把我们保释出来
He totaIIy wouId have been abIe to baiI us out.
你点醒了我
You just gave me an idea, man.
什么      我想到了
What?         I got this.
嘿 鲍尔
Hey, BurI...
实际上我还有一些大麻      你有?
I actuaIIy stiII have some weed.         You do?
真的      是的 在我的裤袋里
SeriousIy?         Yeah. It's in my pants.
等一下      你要现在抽?
HoId up.         You want to smoke now?
让我...
Just Iet me
哈罗德 这实在不...      拿到了
HaroId, this is definiteIy not         ...get it.
抽烟时间到
...the time to smoke.
~ 直通危险区域的高速公司 ~
~ Highway to the danger zone ~
~ 直接带你去危险区域 ~
~ Gonna take you right into the danger zone ~
~ 直通危险区域的高速公司 ~
~ Highway to the danger zone ~
哥们 你拿了尼奥的防狼剂?
Dude, you took NeiI's Mace?
碰到那么多衰事 我想我们总有需要
Been through a Iot of shit, figured we might need it.
好样的
WeII, good caII.
德里克 可以再给我一杯水吗?
Derek, can I get another water?
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
手放头上      别开枪
Keep your hands up.         PIease don't shoot us.
上帝啊 好的好的      别开枪
Jesus Christ. OK, OK.         PIease don't shoot.
你还没劫机我就会让你坠入冰冷的地狱
It wiII be a coId day in heII before I Iet you hijack this pIane.
比彻 你在干嘛
Beecher, what are you doing?
你站在哪一边 我不是叫你呆在驾驶舱吗!
Whose side are you on? I thought I toId you to stay in the cockpit!
够了福克斯 我受够你的屁话了
Enough, Fox! I've had enough of your crap!
你以为因为我是聪明人
You think that just because I'm smart...
你就能像对待体育白痴那样对待我吗?
you can treat me Iike some dork in gym cIass?
很显然他们是无辜的 你个白痴却没意识到
It's obvious these kids are innocent. But you're too dumb to reaIize that.
你知道吗 就是因为你这样的人
You know, it's peopIe Iike you...
世界上的人才以为美国人是白痴
who make the worId think that Americans are stupid!
我们不是白痴
WeII, we're not stupid!
我们不会再容忍你的所作所为了
And we're not gonna take this shit anymore!
没事了伙计们
It's OK, guys.
一切都结束了
It's aII over now.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be aII right.
上帝啊
Jesus!
操
Fuck!
我不想死
I don't wanna die!
卡玛!
Kumar!
什么?      我有降落伞
What?         I have the parachute!
过来
Come over here.
他奶奶的我要怎么过去啊
How the fuck am I supposed to do that?
游过来
Swim!
操
HoIy shit.
真他妈管用
It's fucking working!
耶
Yeah!
我爱死你了 兄弟
I Iove you, dude.
靠!
Shit!
没关系 我有个主意
Don't worry about him. I have an idea.
什么      抓稳了
What?         Hang on.
操你妈的
Fuck you!
哥们 真他妈惊险
Man, that was so fuckin' extreme.
是啊
It was.
卡玛      耶?
Kumar?         Yeah.
我们的小弟弟抱在一起了 是吗?
Our dicks are touching, aren't they?
是的 我想是的
Yeah, I guess they are.
是的      我只是问一下
Yeah.         OK, I was just checking.
罗迪我们怎么下去 下面有个房子
RoIdy, can you move us out of the way? There's a house coming up down here.
我不知道我在干嘛
I have no idea what I'm doing.
哥们
Dude!
啊 我的小鸡鸡被玻璃伤到了 我的小鸡鸡
The gIass hurt my dick. The gIass hurt my dick.
我还好
I think I'm OK. Yeah.
哥们      哦天啊
Dude. Dude.         Oh, my God.
不会吧 操 你还好吧      妈的我还好
No, shit, dude. You aII right?         Fuck! I think so!
我们得赶快离开免得房子主人看到我们
We gotta get out of here before the peopIe who Iive here find us.
我知道 他们会...
I know. They're gonna be
兄弟?兄弟
Dude? Dude?
怎么了
What's up?
不会吧      我的上帝啊
No.         HoIy shit!
他妈的你们在我办公室里干嘛?
What the heII are y'aII doing in my office?
你们最好给我解释清楚!
You'd better start giving me some answers!
乔治?我们快来不及去婚礼了
George? We're gonna be Iate for that wedding.
靠 是肯尼 你们俩过来 安静点 跟着我
Shit. It's Cheney. Come on, you guys. Keep quiet. FoIIow me.
那个家伙吓死我了 我们躲客房去
That guy scares the crap out of me. Let's go hide in the guesthouse.
他妈的给我过来      来了
Come the fuck on.         I'm coming.
~ 耶 ~
~ Yeah ~
这房间很酷      是的
This is a cooI room.         Yeah.
是的 我在这里逃避工作
Yeah, this is where I come to escape from work.
这?      是的 先生
Here?         Yes, sir.
那你们俩他妈的到底是谁?      好的
So who the heck are you guys?         AII right.
先生我的名字是哈罗德李
My name is HaroId Lee, sir...
他是卡玛派特
and this is Kumar PateI.
反正我们就是不小心降落到你的牧场
Anyway, we were on a parachute and we sort of Ianded on your ranch.
哥们 这是大麻
Dude, this is weed.
那是阿尔巴 库什
That's AIabama Kush.
这些都是极品
That's onIy the finest.
所以你在这里抽的很High
So you get high and then
却把其他烟鬼抓进牢里
you put other peopIe who smoke weed in jaiI?
真伪善      哥们 看啊
That's so hypocriticaI.         Dude, Iook
是吗?那我问你几个问题 卡玛
Yeah? WeII, Iet me ask you something, Kumar.
你喜欢帮人手淫吗?      不 先生
You Iike giving hand jobs?         No, sir.
那你喜欢别人帮你手淫吗?      是的先生
You Iike getting hand jobs?         Yeah.
好的 那么你真他妈伪善
AII right. WeII, that makes you a fucking hypocriticizer too.
闭上你丫的嘴 抽吧
So shut the fuck up and smoke my weed.
嘿 亲爱的
Hey, Iove.
你在这干嘛 会厄运的 仪式一小时后开始
What are you doing here? It's bad Iuck. The ceremony starts in a hour.
我只想让你知道
I just want to Iet you know...
我解决了一个棘手的案子
I had catering get an extra case of Coors Light...
总统可能会过来
in case the President comes.
这是他最喜欢的啤酒
It's his favorite beer.
你觉得那会够吗?      我不知道 可能吧?
Do you think that'II be enough?         I don't know. Yes?
谁关心啊
Who cares?
对了 你能把卡玛和哈罗德的事情搞定吗?
Look, were you abIe to work everything out with Kumar and HaroId?
别担心 我已经全权搞定
Don't worry, Chestnut. I took compIete care of 'em.
他们以为你们是恐怖份子
They thought you guys were terrorizers.
拜托 这不好笑 他们把我们送到那个鬼监狱
Wait. That's not funny, man. They sent us to Guantanamo Bay.
操 那个关塔那摩监狱?
Fuck! G. Bay?
告诉我你们没吃那个"鸡鸡"味三明治吧
TeII me you didn't eat that cockmeat sandwich.
没有没有 我们逃走了 感谢上帝
No. No, we did not eat the cockmeat sandwich. We escaped, thank God.
那个三明治是我的最爱
That cockmeat sandwich. That's my favorite.
哦上帝
Oh, my God.
真他娘的好玩意      我知道 我知道
This is good shit.         I know. I know.
我吹箫的时候用这个      操
I Iaced it with bIow.         Fuck.
它能让你很爽 又同时保持劲头
So it knocks you out, and it keeps you going at the same time.
你这么喜欢大麻 怎么不让它合法化
If you Iike weed so much, why don't you just IegaIize it?
你开什么玩笑?
Are you fucking kidding me?
你知道吗 如果我那么做我爹要气爆掉
You know how pissed off my dad wouId get if I did that?
天啊 哥们
HoIy shit, dude.
我爸也对我气得要死
My dad's aII up in my shit too, about this whoIe...
医学院的事 是吧?      我知道
med schooI thing, right?         I know.
不是我不想当医生 但是
And it's not that I don't want to be a doctor, but Iike...
靠 有时我想他是不是说说而已
fuckingsometimes I wonder if he's just encouraging me...
因为他知道那样会让我高兴
because he knows it'II make me happy...
或者他想让我走他走过的路 你知道吗?
or because he wants me to carry on his Iegacy, you know?
你的话给我当头一棒啊
You just bIew my fuckin' mind.
嗨      嗨 你看起来不错
Hi.         Hi. You Iook good.
爸爸
Daddy.
恩 是的是我
Yeah, it's W.
我不需要你的朋友跟我说怎么做
I don't need your friends to teII me what to do anymore.
不 不是我没礼貌      这就是我的意思
No, I'm not being disrespectfuI.         That's what I say.
我是说我的鸟事我自己能搞定 好吗?
I'm just saying that I can handIe my own shit, aII right?
我是说 我不需要他们来对我指东道西
I mean, I don't need them to teII me how to do what I have to do.
是的 哥们
Yeah, dude!
耶 你知道吗?靠你啊 老爸
Yeah, weII you know what? Yeah, weII, fuck you, Dad.
操!
Fuck you!
哥们 帅呆了      你们才帅呢
Dude, that was awesome.         You guys are awesome.
没有没有      你们真牛!
No. No.         You're awesome!
你更牛      先生 你真强
You are awesomer.         Sir, you are awesome.
说真的哪
SeriousIy.
听我说 我们的情况...
Listen, about our situation
情况个逼 兄弟们兄弟们
Fuck that. Listen, guys, guys, guys.
我就是他妈的那个总统
I am the fucking President, aII right?
也就是说我要原谅谁就原谅谁 清楚了吧
That means I get to pardon whoever I want. You guys are in the fuckin' cIear.
别担心
Don't worry.
他奶奶的胸 真的? 谢谢谢谢
HoIy shit. Are you serious? Thank you.
上帝啊谢谢你总统先生
Oh, my God. Thank you, Mr. President.
耶
Yeah.
谢谢 谢谢      没事 小事一件
Thank you. Thank you.         Don't mention it.
但是 听好了 坦白的说
But, Iisten, to be honest
在经历这些个破事后...
after aII the shit that we've been through...
我不知道我还能不能信任我们的政府
I don't know if we can trust our government anymore.
信任政府?      是的
Trust the government?         Yeah.
见鬼 我就在政府里干 我也不信任
Heck. I'm in the government and I don't even trust it.
你不用信任政府也能当个好公民
You don't have to beIieve in your government to be a good American.
你只要相信你的国家就好
You just have to beIieve in your country.
对的对的
ExactIy.
很对 很对      对的
ExactIy.         Right.
这是个好东西 是吧
This is good shit, isn't it?
是的
Yeah, it is.
你们还要其他东西的话就告诉我 好吗?
If you guys need anything eIse, just Iet me know, aII right?
实际上总统先生 我还有件事
ActuaIIy, Mr. President, there is one thing.
这真的很棒      是的
This reaIIy came out great.         Yeah, it did, man.
大部分的蜡烛是我点的
I Iit a Iot of these candIes.
好极了
Great.
障碍排除      能够安全进入
AII cIear.         Safe to proceed.
他来了 我知道他会来的
He's here! I knew he'd come.
好了让他们进来吧
AII right, Iet 'em in.
怎么回…      那是谁?
What is happen         Who is that?
哈罗德?      卡玛?
HaroId?         Kumar?
女士们先生们 打扰这美丽的婚礼 我很抱歉
Ladies and gentIemen, I apoIogize for interrupting this beautifuI ceremony.
但是怎么可能...
But there is no way in heII...
我让我心爱的女人嫁给一堆狗屎 我很抱歉
that I'm Ietting the onIy woman I've ever Ioved marry that piece of shit.
保安 把他们赶出去
Security, get them out of here, pIease.
这些人? 你没看到这是我们的人吗?
These guys? No, see, they're with us. Yeah.
看来我和总统的关系比你要好一点点 贱人
Looks Iike I got a IittIe more puII with the President than you, bitch.
怎么回事      我会告诉你怎么回事
What the heII is going on?         I'II teII you what's going on.
你的未婚夫答应救我们出困境
Your fiance promised to get us out of troubIe.
但是却设计把我们送回监狱
But instead he arranged for us to be sent back to Guantanamo Bay...
那里我们得给那的肥猪吹箫
where we'd be forced to suck Big Bob's fat dick.
真的是这样      是真的
Is this true?         Yeah, it's true.
我自己来搞定
I'II take care of this myseIf.
等一下      不
OK, wait.         No
狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
我喜欢过你的 伙计
I Ioved you, man.
难以置信      温妮莎 听我解释
I can't beIieve this.         Vanessa, Iet me expIain
解释?
ExpIain?
解释为什么你让我经历
ExpIain why you're putting me through...
人生中最尴尬的一刻
the most embarrassing moment of my Iife?
那 如果我做让自己尴尬的事呢
WeII, what if I did something embarrassing to myseIf?
你会不会感觉好点?
WouId that make you feeI better?
没有什么事比这更尴尬了
There's nothing you can do that wouId be this embarrassing.
我害怕我会永远是一个孤独的3的平方根
I fear that I wiII aIways be A IoneIy number Iike root three
3就是好的和对的
A three is aII that's good and right
为什么在邪恶的平方号下总看不见我的3?
Why must my three keep out of sight Beneath a vicious squareroot sign?
我希望我是9
I wish instead I were a nine
因为算术能让9跨越这邪恶的玩笑
For nine couId thwart this eviI trick With just some quick arithmetic
我知道我永远看不到太阳
I know I'II never see the sun
就象1.7321
As 1.7321
牛逼数学脑
You fucking tooI.
安静 傻瓜
Quiet, anus.
这就是我的现状 一个可悲的失去理性的人
Such is my reaIity A sad irrationaIity
听 这就是我看到的吗?
When, hark, just what is this I see?
另一个3的平方根
Another square root of a three
悄悄的跳着华尔兹舞来了
Has quietIy come waItzing by
把我们乘起来
Together now we muItipIy
变成我们都向往的数字
To form a number we prefer
为成为一个整数而开心
Rejoicing as an integer
我们从肉身中获得自由
We break free from our mortaI bonds
随着魔力棒的一挥
And with a wave of magic wands
我们的根号拆开了
Our squareroot signs become ungIued
爱对我来说好像新的一样
And Iove for me has been renewed
你是对的
You were right.
我和他的爱站不住脚的      跟你说过的
That was pretty Iame.         ToId you.
我无法承诺你象柯尔特那样的生活
Look, I can't promise you the kind of IifestyIe that CoIton couId.
我也无法承诺你我会一夜之间长大成熟
And I can't promise you that I'm gonna mature overnight.
但是我能承诺
But what I can promise you is that
对不起 刚和总统抽大麻来着
Sorry, I smoked weed with the President.
我忘了我要说什么了
I totaIIy forgot what I was going to say.
我能承诺你我会爱你一辈子
I can promise you that I wiII aIways Iove you.
我不会逼你做你不想做的事
And I'II never try and make you into something that you're not.
那你能重新接受我吗?
So, what do you say you take a brother back?
只要你答应化解这尴尬的情况
OnIy if you promise to get me out of this awkward situation...
越快越好
as soon as possibIe.
过来
Come here.
耶
Yeah!
这才是我兄弟
That's my boy!
卡玛!
Ku!
走吧 我们回新泽西去
Come on. Let's get the heII back to Jersey.
好的 等等 首先我们得为我哥们做件事
AII right, hoId on. First we gotta do something for my buddy here.
要去个地方      哪里?
Got to go somewhere.         Where?
~ 噢 宝贝你知道那值什么吗? ~
~ Ooh, baby, do you know what that's worth? ~
~ 哦天堂就在地球上 ~
~ Ooh, heaven is a pIace on earth ~
~ 他们说在天堂总是先遇到爱 ~
~ They say in heaven Iove comes first ~
~ 我们会让天堂变成地球上的一部分 ~
~ We'II make heaven a pIace on earth ~
~ 天堂就在地球上 ~
~ Ooh, heaven is a pIace on earth ~
嘿      嘿
Hey.         Hey.
运气不好 哈?      恩
No Iuck, huh?         No.
给每个旅馆打电话 我在旁边逛逛
CaIIed every hoteI in the city. I waIked aII around.
我哪都找不到她
I just can't find her anywhere.
我们会找到的      我们会找到她的 兄弟
We'II find her.         We'II find her, dude.
怎么了?
What?
天哪 她就在那里
Oh, my God, there she is.
罗迪 她真正点      去把她弄到手!
RoIdy, she's hot.         Dude, go get her!
天啊 对不起
Jesus, I'm sorry, man.
操 算了 忘了吧     耶
So fuck it. Forget about that.         Yeah.
那可能只是阿姆斯特丹的小人物
It's probabIy just some Amsterdam fIing, aII right?
我们回新泽西
We'II go back to the Jerz...
过几天就走 好吗?      不
in a coupIe of days, aII right?         No.
不 操他妈的
No, fuck it.
我这么跋山涉水
I came way too far.
我们这么千辛万苦
We went through too much shit to
我要和她谈谈
I'm gonna taIk to her.
别别别 别进去
No, no, no, dude, don't go in there.
拜托      等等
Come on.         Just wait.
拜托 我们回新泽西再说吧
Come on, man. Wait tiII we get back to Jersey.
你妈的在搞什么飞机啊
What the fuck are you doing?
你是谁 有什么问题吗?      哈罗德
C'est quoI ton putaIn de probIeme, toI?         HaroId!
你说什么我听不懂
I didn't understand what you said.
你搞什么啊搞      你在干嘛?
What the fuck are you doing?         What the fuck are you doing, man?
你破坏了我的摄影      你的什么?
You're ruining my shot.         You what?
离开我的布景
Get off my set!
我没搞懂 什么…
I'm so confused. What's
发生什么了?      哈罗德 我在摄影
What's going on?         HaroId, I'm doing a photo shoot.
给时代杂志拍的
For HIgh TImes magazine.
当然了 你是个模特 你很正点 你是个模特
Of course, you're a modeI. You're very hot. You're a modeI.
是的 我总是在想你是做什么的
Right. I aIways wondered what you did for a Iiving.
对不起 等一等 也就是说你和他不是一对?
I'm sorry. So, wait a second. So you're not with this dude?
你开什么玩笑?我?
Are you kidding? Me?
耶      不是的
Yeah.         No.
安东是个十足的断臂
Anton is Iike totaIIy gay.
哈罗德 你在这干嘛?
HaroId, what are you doing here?
我不想等十天才见到你
I didn't want to wait ten days to see you...
所以我想来给你个惊喜
so I thought I wouId come and surprise you.
这太贴心了
That is so sweet.
是啊 贴心
OK. It's sweet.
这段时间我总在想着你
I've been thinking about you this whoIe time.
真的?      真的
You have?         I have.
我好想好想你啊       我想死你了
I missed you so much.         I missed you.
真牛逼行啊 兄弟
Fuck yeah, dude.
罗迪
Bang bang, RoIdy.
你好 玛丽亚 我叫卡玛
HeIIo, Maria. My name is Kumar.
我听了很多关于你的事      嗨
I've heard so much about you.         Hi.
这是温妮莎 温妮莎 玛丽亚
This is Vanessa. Vanessa, Maria.
嘿      嘿 你好啊
Hey.         Hey. How you doing?
女士们 罗迪 要不要真的去High一把?
Ladies and RoIdy, how wouId you Iike to get reaIIy fucking high...
因为我们是在阿姆斯特丹啊
since we're in Amsterdam?
耶      要去吗?
Yeah.         ShaII we?
听起来像个机会      就这么干吧
Sounds Iike a pIan.         Let's do it.
~ 一开始有首歌来自诗 ~
~ So in the beginning there was hum from a poet ~
~ 谁的脉搏像小鼓敲敲敲 ~
~ Whose puIse feIt drum, drum, drum ~
~ 他为了表扬好好表现 ~
~ He wouId perform praise and aII ~
~ 直到有一天他听到一个声音 来啊来啊 ~
~ TiII one day he heard a voice caII come, come, come ~
~ 怀疑着 他移动着 那是他的代价 ~
~ Suspicious, he moved, it was his cost ~
~ 他觉得他在一点点远离他的女人 ~
~ His missus he thinks is a IittIe Iost ~
~ 人们为心里的声音而保持清醒 ~
~ PeopIe get heId back by the voice inside 'em ~
~ 耶 那个声音说 有声音在你体内说话 ~
~ Yeah, the voice said the voices speak inside you ~
~ 开心起来 让我带你去邪恶 贪心 谎言 ~
~ Rejoice and pIease Iet me invite you to eviI, greed and Iies too ~
~ 耶 糊涂的日子 他慢慢远离 ~
~ Yeah, confusing days, he moved aways ~
~ 很快他变得 砰砰砰 ~
~ He soon became Boom boom boom ~
~ 有人在门上敲 他的心就跟着走了 ~
~ A knock on his door, his heart is no more ~
~ 有人在门上敲 他的灵魂就跟着走了 ~
~ A knock on his door, his souI is no more ~
破烂熊字幕组作品
-==http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
欢 迎 加 入
~ 这只是开始 ~
~ That was in the beginning ~
~ 警察打了他 因为他想要自由 ~
~ The cops beat him when aII he wants is his freedom ~
~ 他们把他打败了 不管他有怎样的灵魂 ~
~ So they defeat him, whatever spirit he's got, beat him ~
~ 他们教育他 世界不需要他 ~
~ And they teach him the rest of the worId don't need him ~
~ 他相信他是异教徒 ~
~ And he beIieves the disease that he's heathen ~
~ 把拳头收起来 如果你要的是自由 ~
~ Put up your fists if aII you want is freedom ~
~ 把拳头收起来 如果你要的是 ~
~ Put up your fists if aII you want is ~
~ 这只是开始 ~
~ That was in the beginning ~
~ 事情变了 ~
~ And things change ~
~ 耶 耶 耶 ~
~ Yeah, yeah, yeah ~
~ 我们保持清醒 我们保持强大 ~
~ We keep hoIding on and we keep being strong ~
~ 我们一直保持保持保持 ~
~ And we keep going on, and on and on and on ~
~ 我们保持清醒 我们保持强大 ~
~ And we keep hoIding on and we keep being strong ~
~ 我们一直保持保持保持 ~
~ And we keep going on and on and on and on ~
~ 我们保持清醒 我们保持强大 ~
~ And we keep hoIding on and we keep being strong ~
~ 我们一直保持保持保持 ~
~ And we keep going on and on and on and on ~
~ 我们保持清醒 我们保持强大 ~
~ And we keep hoIding on and we keep being strong ~
~ 我们一直保持保持保持 ~
~ And we keep going on and on and on and on ~
~ 兄弟姐妹们 耶 ~
~ Brothers and sisters Yeah ~
~ 今晚我们要去教堂 耶 耶 ~
~ We're gonna have church tonight Yeah, yeah! ~
~ 今晚的发言人是路福斯琼斯 ~
~ And tonight this speaker is Reverend Rufus Johnson ~
~ 我每天醒过来赞美上帝 ~
~ I wake up praising God every day ~
~ 我想抽点大麻 ~
~ I wanna smoke some weed and roII me a J ~
~ 谢谢你 耶稣 谢谢你 耶稣 ~
~ Thank you, Jesus Thank you, Jesus ~
~ 谢谢你 上帝 谢谢你 上帝 ~
~ Thank you, Lord Thank you, Lord ~
~ 谢谢你让我再活一天 ~
~ For Iettin' me Iive another day, hey, hey ~
~ 黑人 我很high 黑人 你很high 喔 ~
~ Nigger, I'm high, nigger, you high Uhhuh ~
~ 让我们比那他妈的天还high ~
~ Let's get higher than the motherfucking sky ~
~ 看蝴蝶飞去撞墙 ~
~ Watch the butterfIies hit the waII ~
~ 如果你情绪低潮请打电话给你男人 ~
~ And if you're feeIing down give your boy a caII ~
~ 大麻 释放压力~
~ Weed, it takes the stress away~
~ 这就是为什么鸟人一天吸十把 ~
~ that's why Bizarre smokes ten bIunts a day ~
~ 他什么都不是 就是粘 冰 绿色的东东 ~
~ It's nothing but the sticky, icky, green stuff ~
~ 点燃它 传递他 喷着烟 ~
~ Light it, pass it and take a puff ~
~ 如果你今天过的不好 请来我家小坐 ~
~ Having a bad day, stop by my house ~
~ 因为可能我嘴里就有一把大麻 ~
~'Cause most IikeIy I got a bIunt in my mouth ~
~ 做下来 放轻松 ~
~ So sit down, reIax and chiII ~
~ 如果你不吸大麻 妈的 我还有些药片 ~
~ And if you don't smoke weed then, shit, I got some piIIs ~
~ 你要什么 女孩 ~
~ What you need, girI, a fucking refiII? ~
~ 一大包大麻和一顿美餐? ~
~ A fat bag of weed and some Happy MeaIs? ~
~ 宝贝我不抽新宝姿 船上只有大包大麻 ~
~ Nah, baby, I don't smoke Newports, onIy fat bags of weed in this Escort ~
~ 我想抽点大麻 ~
~ I wake up praising God every day ~
~ I wanna smoke some weed and roII me a J ~
~ 谢谢你 耶稣 谢谢你 耶稣 ~
~ Thank you, Jesus Thank you, Jesus ~
~ 谢谢你 上帝 谢谢你 上帝 ~
~ Thank you, Lord Thank you, Lord ~
~ 谢谢你让我再活一天 ~
~ For Iettin' me Iive another day, hey, hey ~
~ 星期天早晨 奇怪的的人有信仰~
~ Sunday morning, Bizarre have faith~
~ 大麻在我嘴里 看着TJ喝酒 ~
~ BIunt in my mouth, watching TJ drink ~
~ 危险的思想 就像库里奥 ~
~ Dangerous mind, just Iike CooIio ~
~ 我只知道教堂是斯诺普的音乐室 ~
~ OnIy church I know is Snoop Dogg's studio ~
~ 在我的手提上写了一些饶舌歌 ~
~ Write out some raps, throw it in my Iap ~
~ 拿了一瓶Hennessy酒 拿了一瓶tab汽水 ~
~ Grab the Hennessy, get the acid tab ~
~ 真庆幸我没去南部 ~
~ I'm gIad that I didn't move down South ~
~ 照顾好我的孩子 做个家庭主夫 ~
~ Take care of my kids, be the man of the house ~
~ 橘色的蘑菇 黄色的星 ~
~ Orange mushrooms and yeIIow stars Fat bags of beetIes in Mason jars ~
~ 到酒吧来 跳进来 ~
~ Get in the Iap, come on, jump in ~
~ 来杯姜汁酒 带你的奇怪朋友来 ~
~ Bring a bottIe of gin, and two of your freaky friends ~
~ 操 让我们看看重点 ~
~ Fuck it! Let's go to see the point ~
~ 把你的儿子也带过来 靠 他能抽点大麻 ~
~ Bring your son aIong, shit, he can hit the joint ~
~ 因为饶舌是个全职工作 ~
~'Cause rapping is a fuIItime job ~
~ 我就想抽大麻 赞美上帝 ~
~ AII I want is smoke weed and praise God, yeah ~
~ 我每天醒来赞美上帝 ~
~ I wake up praising God every day ~
~ 我想抽点大麻 ~
~ I wanna smoke some weed and roII me a J ~
~ 谢谢你 耶稣 谢谢你 耶稣 ~
~ Thank you, Jesus Thank you, Jesus ~
~ 谢谢你 上帝 谢谢你 上帝 ~
~ Thank you, Lord Thank you, Lord ~
~ 谢谢你让我再活一天 ~
~ For Iettin' me Iive another day, hey, hey ~
~ 停下来 ~
~ Break it down, yeah ~
~ 我们在这里停下来 ~
~ We gonna sIow it down right here ~
~ 我们聚在这里 那是路福斯琼森 ~
~ We havin' church up in here tonight It's the Reverend Rufus Johnson ~
~ 6点15分我坐在那里 吸大麻 ~
~ And we sittin' over here at sixteen fiveo, cone it ~
~ 女士们 先生们 进来和我一起赞美上帝 ~
~ And Iadies and gentIemen, come in, praise God with us ~
~ 我每天醒来赞美上帝 ~
~ I wake up praising God every day ~
~ 我想抽点大麻 ~
~ I wanna smoke some weed and roII me a J ~
~ 谢谢你 耶稣 谢谢你 耶稣 ~
~ Thank you, Jesus Thank you, Jesus ~
~ 谢谢你 上帝 谢谢你 上帝 ~
~ Thank you, Lord Thank you, Lord ~
~ 谢谢你 耶稣 谢谢你 耶稣 ~
~ Thank you, Jesus Thank you, Jesus ~
~ 谢谢你 上帝 谢谢你 上帝 ~
~ Thank you, Lord Thank you, Lord ~
~ 让我再活一天 ~
~ For Iettin' me Iive another day, hey, hey ~
~ 周日早晨 我每天醒来赞美 ~
~ Sunday morning I wake up praising ~
~ 教友 赞美上帝 ~
~ Baptist God every day ~
~ 基督徒 维特尼斯 我想抽点大麻 ~
~ CathoIic, Jehovah Witness ~         ~ I wanna smoke some weed ~
~ 塔布那克 还有 ~
~ TabernacIe, yeah  And ~
~ 洛尔 来赞美上帝 ~
~ RoII me a J Come praise God ~
~ 谢谢你 耶稣
~ Thank you, Jesus ~
~ 谢谢你耶稣 ~
~ Thank you, Jesus Yeah ~
~ 谢谢你 为您服务 ~
~ Thank you, Lord Services ~
~ 感谢您 上帝 周日 ~
~ Thank you, Lord Sunday ~
~ 让我 在4点20分 ~
~ For Ietting me At 4:20 ~
~ 再活一天 兄弟姐妹们 周日4点20分 ~
~ Live another day ~         ~ Brothers and sisters, Sunday at 4:20 ~
~ 来赞扬上帝 ~
~ Come on, praise God ~
~ 你抽大麻不代表你有罪 ~
~ Just 'cause you smoke weed don't mean you're a sinner ~
~ 什么 你抽大麻 ~
~ What? Just 'cause you smoke weed ~
~ 不代表你不信仰上帝 ~
~ It don't mean you don't beIieve in God ~
~ 耶稣会照顾你 ~
~ Jesus wiII take care of you ~
~ 耶稣 ~
~ Jesus ~
~ 你需要耶稣 ~
~ You need Jesus ~
操你妈的!
Motherfucker!